like again first of all like this
como otra vez antes que nada como esto
how are my people do
cómo está mi gente
you want to give each other or not we can talk about life
queréis darse o no hablamos de la vida
we ​​could talk about life today is a
podríamos hablar de la vida hoy es un
very hot day
día muy caluroso
[Music] I
[Música]
was saying welcome to welcome we are
decía bienvenida a la bienvenida estamos
at 60 well already less than 60 for sure we are
a 60 bueno ya menos de 60 seguro estamos
less than 60 members away from reaching 800
a menos de 60 miembros para llegar a 800
members on the channel this Javier canino it
miembros en el canal este javier canino
would seem crazy to me it would seem
me parecería una locura me parecería una
crazy to arrive today today today I see it
locura llegar hoy hoy hoy lo veo
complicated I see it complicated I don't know if you
complicado lo veo complicado no sé si me
love me that much but it would be good it would be good
queréis tanto pero estaría bien estaría
let your hands okay don't
bien lo dejan vuestras manos vale no
let your hands I know that many of
dejan vuestras manos yo sé que muchos de
you
ustedes
I know that many of you are going to
yo sé que muchos de ustedes os vais a
end up becoming members
acabar haciendo miembros
sooner or later I'm going to end up
más tarde o más temprano os voy a acabar
making you members so I
haciendo miembros entonces yo me
wonder
pregunto
[Music] is there
[Música]
more welcome welcome
hay más bienvenida bienvenida
Javier to
javier a
[Music]
[Música]
I wonder
yo me pregunto
and cream welcome
y nata bienvenida
[Music]
[Música]
Belen Romero
belen romero
will have thank you very much thank you very much and
tendrá muchas gracias muchas gracias y
a hug churra a pleasure to come back
un abrazo churra un gusto volver por
here even if it's just for a little while radiant face
aquí aunque sea un ratito cara radiante
with smiling eyes greetings of
con ojos sonrientes un saludo desde
course well radiant face for you  this
luego pues yo cara radiante para ti está
goal to javi handsome smiling face with
gol a javi guapo cara sonriendo con ojos
heart eyes recorded for something the salsero
de corazón grabadas por algo el salsero
party face smiling face with
cara de fiesta cara sonriendo con ojos
heart eyes I like your party face
de corazón me gusta tu cara de fiesta
see milestone a party face for
ver hito una cara de fiesta también para
you too although I'm tired okay I've been I
ti aunque yo estoy cansado vale llevo
'm exhausted I'm not going to lie it shows
estoy agotado no voy a mentir se me nota
a little on my face no I'm a little
un poco en la cara no estoy un poco
tired because the [ __ ] is it or three hours
cansado porque está o tres horas en
live now with roba to youtube if
directo ahora con roba a youtube si
now with HIV you can't complain you can't
ahora con vih no podéis quejar no os
complain I wouldn't be surprised at all if
podéis quejar no me extrañaría nada que
we reached 800 members I wouldn't be
llegásemos a 800 miembros no me
surprised because I know that you
extrañaría porque yo sé que ustedes me
love me what happens is I know that you're not going to
queréis lo que pasa que sé que no lo
do it for the four heras fed
vais a hacer por las four heras
up
arto
[Music]
[Música]
artur welcome welcome I think that
artur bienvenido bienvenido yo creo que
artur will be the last member of the night
artur será el último miembro de la noche
I know that you look and for the forum members
yo sé que ustedes mira y por las foreras
and despite the fact that I think that it has been
y a pesar de que yo creo que ya ha sido
enough that in the
suficiente con que en el directo
previous live on you know we have reached
anterior en you know hayamos llegado
almost 300,000 light
casi a 300.000 light
I think that from now on you
yo creo que ya ustedes a partir de ahora
are going to look out for them and you are not going to
vais a mirar por ellas y no le vais a
do so much harm because the [ __ ] these things
hacer tanto daño porque estas cosas
to them  it hurts them to remember that they
a ellas les duele recordar que ellas
are there counting all the members
están ahí contando todos los miembros
that I have on each platform and such and
que tengo en cada plataforma y tal y
then I think that with 750 things and
entonces yo creo que ya con 750 cosas y
what there will be now with those that you have
que habrá ahora con los que se habéis
made now with this life at
hecho ahora ya con esto la vida a la
night this is the 300,000 see you later
noche esto es los 300.000 hasta luego
foreras and these hurt them because they
foreras y a ellas estos les duele porque
have been saying for a year that it was my
llevan un año diciendo que ya era mi
end that I was finished and ruined and
final que yo estaba acabado y la ruina y
such so
tal
thank you on behalf of the bonfires
así que gracias de parte de las fogueras
for not making more members okay I would
por no hacer más miembros vale me
like to start this live like
gustaría empezar este directo al igual
I started the other one
que he empezado el otro
showing this tweet in case there are people who have
mostrando este tuit por si hay gente que
not seen it because it is because this
no lo ha visto porque es porque esto
is also an argument that I had with the
también es una discusión que tuve con la
fonera of her day the subject of my high school graduate let's
fonera de su día el tema de mi graduado
see guys I said it
a ver chicos lo he dicho
so who did they get from the pp or from the
entonces quién se ha sacado del pp o del
ass as most of the
como diría la mayoría de
viewers who are here now would say because it would be
espectadores que estáis ahora porque
from Latin America cap buzzi nice
sería de latinoamérica cap buzzi bonito
name campus chip
nombre campus chip
nicola thank you very much my brother
nicola muchas gracias mi hermano
before you found out that I did not have the
antes habéis sacado que yo no tenía el
degree when I strained I have always said it I
grado al colar yo siempre lo he dicho
was an idiot not to continue with my
fui de no seguir con mi
studies because I was worth it but I saw it mother  she
estudio porque yo valía pero lo vi madre
made me get my school grade because she
me hizo sacarme el grado escolar porque
told me look kids if you lower the
me dijo mira niños si te bajen el
school at least this the gradual
colegio por lo menos esto el gradual
cola would finish it gave it to you but that you
cola lo terminaba le dio sino que te
cut it and put a blanket for the
corte y de meter una manta para los
babies subdued do not tell me to my mother to
bebés sometidas no me dices a mi madre a
my mother very peaceful but she told me
mi madre muy pacífica pero me dijo que
hey do you refuse to redrado with the
oye que te niegas a redrado con la por
at least because it was not going to be a because
lo menos porque no iba a ser un porque
tomorrow she told me that from Javi the
el día de mañana me dijo que de javi el
gradual cola you are going to get it because
gradual colar te lo vas a sacar porque
tomorrow
el día de mañana
[Music]
[Música]
Mariel here I take you Mariel enough enough I do
mariel aquí te llevo mariel ya basta ya
n't know what is more disgusting the thread
basta no sé qué es más asqueroso el hilo
itself or that they chose to do it right
en sí o que hayan escogido hacerlo justo
after Dallas' birthday right
después del cumpleaños de dallas justo
after I don't think it was actually
después no creo que en realidad se
published the same day because for me this
publicó el mismo día porque a mí esto
yesterday I was already expecting it cloth I
ayer ya me lo estaba esperando tela lo
passed it as we have the debate of Rome and
pasé como tenemos el debate de roma y
Gran well we did not see it in my mother she
gran pues no lo vimos en mi madre me
told me the gradual cola you have to
dijo el gradual cola te lo tienes que
get it okay because tomorrow there will
sacar vale porque el día de mañana va a
be a forum that will tell you that you do not
haber un foro que te va a decir que no
have the graduate and there will be a
tienes el graduado y va a haber un
youtuber there will
youtuber
be a youtube that will be
va a haber un youtube que te va a tener
very scared of you and  values ​​​​you a lot he is going to
mucho miedo y valora mucho contigo va a
cry a lot with you because he has been
llorar mucho contigo porque ha estado
abusing, messing with everyone,
abusando de meterse con todo el mundo
no one answered him
nadie la respondió
or no one answered him also like you, you
o nadie le respondió también como tú tú
answered her so much his mouth has lost I
la respondió la tanto la boca ha perdido
know how many followers because you have
lo sé cuántos seguidores porque tú has
exposed the truth and people
expuesto la verdad y la gente se da
realize what it is like and the guy is going to be
cuenta de cómo es y el tío va a estar
crying saying that he is going to report you that I am
llorando diciendo que te va a denunciar
going to report him imagine a
que lo voy a denunciar imaginaros una
complaint from Joan Plana it is true I
denuncia de joan plana es verdad yo en
really do not know if he is saying it because of so
realidad no sé si lo está diciendo por
much or in his mind
tanto o en su mente
with his hands with the movements he
con los manos con los movimientos que
makes you put it imagine that the lawsuit reaches me
hace la pones imaginaros que me llega la
and for that reason because you have
demanda y por eso porque tú has
insulted Joan Plana it
insultado a joan plana
is my first donation to a streamer and I
es mi primera donación a un streamer y
give it to you thank you for the
te los doy a ti gracias por el
entertainment and for the sal xeito
entretenimiento y por el sal xeito un
greetings from Ecuador thanks to llama
saludo desde ecuador gracias a llama
touched all my heart with that of the
tocado todo el corazón con eso de la
first and more touched my heart
primera e más tocado el corazón muchas
thank you very much king and imagine the complaint it
gracias rey y imaginar a la denuncia no
is not that Javier and measured more said fool and that he sucks his
es que javier y medida más dicho tonto y
[ __ ] and that okay said is that
que le chupe la y que vale dicho
in reality insults as such I
sea que en realidad insultos como tal yo
could tell him
que le podía decir
go to hell organized with things like
vete a la organizada con cosas
that after he calls me abuse
así después de que me llame maltrato
all without neurons
todo sin neuronas
with the disease
con la enfermedad
[Music]
[Música]
robinson
robinson
thank you very much
muchas gracias
the lawsuit the shot and the desire Victor
la demanda el tiro y la ganas víctor
Daniel thank you very much Rey
daniel muchas gracias rey
and then for image rights he wants to
y luego por derecho a la imagen quiere
sue me for image rights
denunciar me por derecho a la imagen
because I have put clips of his in my
porque yo he puesto clips suyos en mis
videos when he has also put mine did you
vídeos cuando él también los ha puesto
imagine that Jon Plana is the
se imaginaron que jon plana es el
pioneer in winning a lawsuit for
pionero en ganar una demanda por derecho
image rights when he has signed the
a la imagen cuando él ha firmado en
terms on Twitter and YouTube
twitter en youtube los términos
accepting that his content be used
aceptando que se utilice su contenido
which are videos that he has published
que son vídeos que él ha publicado
when he also does it with others
cuando él también lo hace con los demás
I think he wins that lawsuit but did you
yo creo que esa demanda la gana pero
see the last tweets from Dallas come on
viste los últimos tweets de dallas vamos
please we are in no hurry John
por favor estamos sin prisa jhon
Alexander thank you very much for your super
alexander muchas gracias por tu súper
chat but we are calm now well
chat pero estamos de tranqui ahora bueno
baby I'm doing a little intro it
nene estoy haciendo una pequeña intro
makes people laugh a lot that
me hace mucha gracia a la gente que
when I do the whole
cuando yo hago todo el extracto de
live extract he tells me habib live to the subject
directo me dice habib en directo al tema
what are you doing an intro of 10,000 I do whatever
qué haces una intro de 10.000 hago lo
the hell I
que me sale de la
do whatever the hell I do or light
hago lo que me sale de la o light
aro is General Oscar thank you very much
aro es el general óscar muchas gracias
on my channel and this is a
en mi canal y esto es un extracto de
live extract for  put it on the chili it doesn't
directo para ponérselo del chile no
matter the minutes
importan los minutos
we have our whole lives to skip you're
tenemos toda la vida para saltear eres
great I love you uncle tsuru
genial te quiero tío tsuru
I love you too spend a lot
yo también te quiero gastar muchísimo
for what you've said many things many
por lo que has dicho muchas cosas muchas
things the
cosas
day before yesterday my boyfriend died your live streams
antier murió mi novio tus directos me
help me crack wow
ayudan crack
he kind of put me off a bit I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I do
vaya él me ha cortado el rollo un poco
n't know what whatever the
no sé cuál cualquiera que haya sido la
cause was I'm so sorry from the bottom of my heart I'm glad I'm
causa lo siento muchísimo de corazón me
glad they can be of some use to you I'm
alegro me alegro que te puedan servir de
direct I'm so sorry
algo me directo lo siento muchísimo de
really you have all my condolences to
verdad tienes todo mi pésame que
tell you several things okay
contaros varias cosas vale
my mother told me that the thing about the flower
mi madre me dijo eso el tema de la flor
was that there was a youtuber who was going to
era que había un youtuber que me iba a
such and such
tal y tal
total that Joan Plana I can't say what she
total que joan plana no puedo decir lo
said visual from Colombia but I don't know
que dijo visual de colombia pero no sé
why I love the salsa singer from Spain what's
porque me encanta el salsero de españa
Javi talking about look tonight I'm not drinking
que cuenta javi mira esta noche no tomo
beer and I'm giving you that money hugs
cerveza y te doy esa plata a ti abrazos
thank you very much for
muchas gracias por
thank you very much for sacrificing your beer
muchas gracias por sacrificar tu cerveza
for me it's the nicest thing
por mí es lo más bonito que ha hecho
anyone has done for me today
alguien por mí en el día de hoy
my wife made me a coffee this morning
mi mujer me hizo un café esta mañana
when I got up but I'll
cuando me levanté pero tú cerveza las
bring your beer here I'm telling you seriously in
llevo aquí te lo digo en serio en el
total that  joan plan to the one who has broken
total que joan plan al que ha faltado a
the promise to the condition that
la promesa a la condición que le puso
gallardo put clothes on him that he would debate with him in
ropa gallardo de que debatía con él a
exchange for then he would debate with me,
cambio de que luego debatirá conmigo a
that was missing then he put another
faltaba eso luego puso otra condición
absurd condition saying that he would debate
absurda diciendo que que debatiría
with me when I finished my basic studies
conmigo cuando yo me sacara los estudios
and he screwed up just seriously he gave me
y la ha cagado solo en serio me ha dado
everything sent 20,000 light I can't
en serio todo lo mandado 20.000 light no
believe it you're [ __ ] kidding me you
me lo puedo creer me estáis vacilando
're [ __ ] kidding me I throw everything
me estáis vacilando tiro todo lo
enormous I position myself at your feet enormous everything
enorme me postura a tus pies enorme todo
for what do you get into these messes and you're not going to
para que te metes en estos fregados y no
accept
vas a aceptar
here okay we can put it here the
aquí vale lo podemos poner aquí los
direct positions with clothes but in case
puestos directos con ropa pero por si
someone wasn't always there I have said
alguien no estaba siempre lo he dicho
I have a high school diploma okay I was an
tengo el graduado escolar vale fui
idiot I should have studied
tenía que haber estudiado
a lot more because I was a guy in
muchísimo más porque yo era un tío en
chicken deep outstanding but I was an
pollo hondo sobresaliente pero fui
idiot I believed that I was sorry a
me creía que de lamentar un
pimp for getting to work checked
chulo por ponerme a trabajar comprobado
before interrupting now yes I can send
antes interrumpir ahora sí puedo mandar
super chat about dallas face crying
súper chat sobre dallas cara llorando
hard it's that his last tweet left me
fuerte es que su último tuit me dejó
very very intrigued here we go we're
mucho muy intrigado aquí vamos
not going to remove all your intrigues
no vamos a quitar todas tus intrigas
because I can't tell it  everything but well let's go let's
porque no puedo contarlo todo pero bueno
see everything let's
vamos a vamos a verlo todo vamos a
analyze everything with
analizarlo todo con calma
total calm here also next to the tail and if
total aquí también lado al cola y si
now someone wants to use the excuse and
ahora alguien quiere poner la excusa y
wants to say that I have falsified this
quiere decir que yo he falsificado esto
accusing me of falsifying a document be
acusándome de falsificar un documento
careful very careful and also
cuidado mucho cuidado y además
from here I challenge whoever wants to
desde aquí retó a quien quiera a que
come to Seville with me with a camera
venga a sevilla conmigo con una cámara
we are going to go to the slaughterhouse because those of you who are
vamos a ir al matadero que los que seáis
from Seville know how difficult the
de sevilla sabéis qué difícil es el
slaughterhouse building is there is a front the
edificio del matadero hay un frente los
birds
pajaritos
I ask for a duplicate and we will see if this is true
pido duplicado y vemos si esto es verdad
lie okay that on the one hand this
mentira vale eso por una parte este
system thanks see you welcome to the
sistema gracias verte bienvenido al
center half an hour if we have more
centro de media hora si tenemos más
time from here we are in no hurry Louis
tiempo de aquí no tenemos prisa louis
we are with the chip
estamos del chip
okay you must we are with
vale debes
the chili but do not make more
estamos del chile pero no hagáis más
members what I have made to the flower was it bothers them what I have done
miembros que he hecho a la flor era les
to the ears they don't like it I do
que he hecho a las orejas no les gusta
n't think we will reach 800 members today
no creo que lleguemos a 800 miembros hoy
no I don't
no
know it would be too much did you throw what are you
no sé sería mucho tiraron ustedes qué
betting let's see I want to see the chat we
apostáis a ver quiero ver el chat
reached 808 it did not
llegamos a 808 no
reach 808 no josé agua you have
llegaba a 808 no josé agua nos has
worked more than me they must earn the
trabajado más que yo han de ganar el
salary they have acquitted me things and very
sueldo me han absuelto las cosas y muy
ready the breakfasts  looked at you now
listos los desayunos mirado de you now
look at us from you know those of you
míranos de you know los que estáis
being those of youtube that we reach
siendo los de youtube que lleguemos a
800 members now I say to those of
800 miembros ahora yo les digo a los de
youtube
youtube
and what happens with those of Yuna or do we reach
y qué pasa con los de yuna o llegamos a
200 members that I am very smart and we are
200 miembros que soy muy listo y estamos
in 130 days it would be three months
en 130 das sería tres meses
well
bueno
as you all know the little neighbor lives
como todos sabéis el vecino pequeño vive
his brother
su hermano
the identity to the human being
la identidad al ser humano
to his brother
a su hermano
if the human being before starting with
si el ser humano ante empezar con el
today's sanse
sanse de hoy
[Music]
[Música]
misty blue this
misty blue este club
female or male club with that I reach
femenino o masculino con eso me alcanza
javi here they are naming han re that
a javi acá andan nombrando a han re que
nothing face with hand over their mouth I don't
nada cara con mano sobre la boca yo no
know who has complained and I know what has
sé quienes han reclamado y sé lo que ha
happened I have no [ __ ] idea what you
pasado no tengo ni idea de lo que
are talking about I
me estáis hablando
force him to be is that he is his brother I
yo lo obligó de ser es que él su hermano
tell you this as
esto te lo digo como crítica
constructive criticism Mariana thank you very much
constructiva mariana muchísimas gracias
sweetheart
corazón
this is a constructive criticism south
esto es una crítica constructiva sur
people say that you are very impartial
la gente dice que tú eres muy imparcial
I want to trust that you are Javier
yo quiero confiar en que lo eres javier
is the first youtuber that I follow and I become a
es el primer youtuber que sigo y me hago
member I have been watching you since
miembro llevo viéndote desde que empezó
the quarantine began and in eight months I have
la cuarentena y en ocho meses me he
seen a thousand  your videos
visto mil vídeos tuyos
cr here the live shows help me with
cr acá los directos me ayudan con la
depression and turn off the long
depresión y apagarlos largos días de
work days much better thanks javier
trabajo mucho mejor gracias javier
thanks and churra thanks to you to you
gracias y churra gracias a ti a ti
people when they throw hate at me when
la gente cuando me tira hate cuando
we give our opinion on the subject about the
opinamos sobre el tema sobre las
Dallas controversies I take this opportunity to
polémicas de dallas aprovecho para
say it here because this deal is going to be
decirlo aquí porque este trato va a ir
about giving them value they tell me that I
sobre darlas valer me dicen que yo no
am not impartial because I always said I
soy imparcial porque siempre decía lo
defend it that they prefer to know the south
defiendo que prefieren en saber al sur
that is more impartial
que es más imparcial
sun
sol
you know
tú sabes
that going back a little bit the channel with
que remontarse un poquito el canal con
all the controversy of the tula against the la just like like
toda la polémica de la tula en contra de
focus and such
la la igual que al igual que focus y tal
something happened yesterday well the day before yesterday
pasó una cosa ayer bueno antes de ayer
that I don't understand Maria he thank you very much
que yo no entiendo maría él muchas
I don't understand the south I
gracias yo no entiendo el sur me
would like you to explain to me if there is a
gustaría que me a explicar si existe una
reaction to the Dallas video about grave
reacción al vídeo de dallas sobre grave
and the alleged pyramid scam
y la supuesta estafa piramidal
has not uploaded that reaction south
no ha subido esa reacción sur
what has happened
qué ha pasado
because has not uploaded that reaction
porque no ha subido esa reacción
[Music]
[Música]
serna
serna
watching it because I am a member
he estado viéndola porque yo soy miembro
of the south and I have been watching it
del sur y estado viéndola
and the surf in that reaction well he argues
y el surf en esa reacción pues argumenta
some things that he does not like about the video he
algunas cosas que no le gustan del vídeo
says that he does not like it  normal to listen to
dice que no le parece normal escuchar a
greece 6 years ago that is the psoe
grecia hace 6 años que ese es el psoe
six years ago it is okay and he also says
hace seis años ya vale y también dice
but he thinks the video is crap in
pero le parece el vídeo una en
general
general
and he also says that he doubts that it is
y también dice que duda de que eso sea
a joke
una chafa
because there is no trial or any
porque no hay ningún juicio ni ninguna
conviction
condena
javi for how to be as handsome
javi para cómo hacer para ser tan guapo
as I
como
do without wanting to and waldir I do it without
lo hago sin querer y waldir lo hago sin
wanting to that I
querer
thank you very much
que yo muchas gracias
sur it calls my attention that you do not
sur me llama la atención que no te
like
parezca
although it has been said that it is a scam or
aunque se ha dicho que es una estafa o
that it does not seem like a big deal or something like that
que no le parece para tanto o algo así
because there is no trial or he archives it or I do
porque no hay un juicio o la archiva o
not know what sur do you remember drake mol
no sé qué sur se acuerda de drake mol
la cuerda de drake vol
la cuerda de drake vol
if we are going to see at this point in the video
si vamos a ver a esta altura del vídeo
but so that people enter the page
pero para que la gente entre a la página
and want to spend their money more than you cr
y quiere gastar su dinero más que tú cr
caracol rolling with laughter
cáscara revolviéndose de la risa un
greetings to almost greetings to cachi
saludo para casi un saludo para cachi
javier is a machine I am addicted to
javier es un máquina soy adicto al
salsa a hug of encouragement and thank you very much
salsero un abrazo de ánimo y muchas
I am a person to whom
gracias soy una persona a la cual está
the product is promoted therefore I do not have to
promocionado el producto por lo tanto no
make it as interesting or
tengo que hacerlo más interesante o
incredible as possible so that people
increíble posible para que la gente
enter the page and want to spend their
entre a la página y quiere gastar sus
money okay you want to be a
dineros vale que tú quieres ser usuario
normal user which is leaving  to leave the money
normal el cual se va a dejar los dineros
in this advertising, that is, they lower
en esta publicidad o sea que se bajan
the money on this website and
los dineros en esta página de internet y
as I say this falls within the
como yo digo esto entra dentro de los
values ​​of each person of each youtuber
valores de cada persona de cada youtuber
in question, I would not sponsor a
en cuestión yo no patrocinaría una
page making believe that it is super
página haciendo creer que es súper
easy to win without 500 or 1,800 or 300
sencillo ganar sin 500 o 1.800 o 300
dollars when in reality the
dólares cuando realmente las
possibilities are zero these pages
posibilidades son nulas estas páginas
work illiterate cla flat thanks
funciona analfabeto cla plano gracias
cores were with a type of algorithm
cores eran con un tipo de algoritmo el
which they are always going to win more than they
cual siempre van a ganar más de lo que
lose therefore there will always be
pierden por lo tanto siempre va a haber
more users who do not win than those who
más usuarios que no ganen que los que
win it is obvious this works like
ganen es evidente esto funciona como las
online roulette like casinos like
ruletas online como los casinos como
absolutely everything of course it is like that, I mean they
absolutamente todo claro es así o sea
always give to the bank of course of course
dan a la banca siempre claro claro claro
of the ways, that is, apply some
de los modos o sea aplicar algo de
common sense okay without a greater possibility
sentido común vale sin mayor posibilidad
of the random user winning than
de que gane el usuario random a que gane
the company winning okay these companies are thrown away
la empresa vale se tiran estas empresas
because there were losses I think it is unnecessary for
porque habían pérdidas
me to say it in this
creo que sobra que lo diga yo en este
video so [ __ ] as I say you can
vídeo entonces como ya digo podéis
advertise as much as you want but I think
de publicidad lo que queráis pero creo
that honesty drunken
que la honestidad la borrachera
advertising is quite important and
publicidad es bastante importante y
key
clave
at least from my point of view and
por lo menos desde mi punto de vista y
I as  youtube and now welcome and
yo como youtube y ahora bienvenido y
now welcome you see if I do something like
ahora bienvenido tú ver si hago algo de
this I would always try to do it
este estilo siempre intentaría hacerlo
with the greatest honesty possible say
desde la mayor honestidad posible decir
hey their they pay me a lot of money I
oye sus me pagan mucho dinero
don't want you to take this as if you're going to
no quiero que toméis esto como que vais
make the rich of it clear but
a hacer los ricos de la claro pero
when he gives criticism to Greg for the same thing
cuando da la crítica a greg por lo mismo
eight hours there no right Condrey very yes
ocho horas ahí no verdad condrey molt sí
because because it was the era what was
porque porque era la era lo que quedaba
good right let's
bien verdad vamos a
ask you I'm going to ask this
preguntarte yo vamos a preguntar este
south
sur
why didn't you think it was right
porque no te ha parecido bien
why don't you leave didn't you think it was right to
porque no te vas no te ha parecido bien
upload the reaction to the Dallas video and on the
subir la reacción al vídeo de dallas y
way I'll ask you south look the
ya de camino te pregunto sur mira el
road is playing in jail for the
camino está sonando en la cárcel para la
poor 58 year old girl like Felipe did
pobre chica de 58 años como felipe
n't understand well the case south
no entendía bueno el caso sur
were you yourselves the
eras tú te autodenominadas el narrador
official narrator of the tula
oficial de la tula
I find my response to the one about loves very curious
me parece muy curioso mi respuesta a la
[Music] I
[Música]
don't know everything everything absolutely all of the
no sé todo todo absolutamente todos los
tula videos he has reacted he has
vídeos de la tula ha reaccionado él ha
uploaded but nevertheless for some reason
subido pero sin embargo por algún motivo
that I don't know okay I'm not saying it
que desconozco vale no estoy diciendo
's for anything in particular okay I
que sea por nada en concreto vale lo
totally don't know but for some
desconozco totalmente pero por algún
reason
motivo
you had the reaction or to my videos of
tuviste la reacción ni a mis vídeos de
the beach
la playa
where you apologize for questioning or
donde te disculparse por poner en duda o
for what was
por lo que fue
not my last video that closed the anime
ni mi último vídeo que cerraba el anime
of the tula
de la tula
because that
porque eso
if I saw you reacting to colmenar de
si yo te vi reaccionando a colmenar de
la playa because I saw you on the beach after
la playa porque te vi en la playa tras
the 'no they didn't seem good enough to
el 'no no te parecieron buenos como para
upload it
subirlo
[Music] I do
[Música]
n't know each one let's see javi it's obvious that it
no sé cada uno a ver javi es obvio que
's not a scam, the
no es estafa a mí me llegaron las
advertisements that I had to see
publicidades que tenía que ver
daily arrived to me they arrived seven months
diariamente me llegaron siete meses
late but eh they arrived to me each one
tarde pero eh me llegaron cada uno
you can upload what you want of course
puedes subir lo que quiera por supuesto
from the south I'm not going to do anyone to
del sur yo no voy a hacer nadie para
tell you what you have to upload and not
decirte que lo que tienes que subir y no
on your channel but I find it curious that
en tu canal pero me parece curioso que
you get so picky when it comes to
te pongas tan exquisito a la hora de
uploading a reaction or not
subir una reacción o no
when you upload any other things about
cuando sube cualquier otras cosas sobre
any other things
cualquier otras cosas
reacting has made of the voice videos
reaccionando ha hecho de la voz vídeos
of silly topics since I
de temas chorras desde que me
a tweet of folk I make a video of 12 I do
un tuit de folk hago vídeo de 12
n't know it seems strange to me I want to see you
no sé me parece extraño yo te quiero ver
on the beach and make you the canoe
en la playa y hacerte la piragua
and don't tell me those things at these hours
y no me diga esas cosas a estas horas
that are now on top that I am that I have been
que está ahora encima que estoy que me
able to consummate because working at
he podido consumar porque trabajar a
these hours is what has on me you
estas horas es lo que tiene encima se me
put  silly ones we throw no and well
ponéis tontorrones echamos no y bueno
after this little beef to the south that I
después de este pequeño beef al sur que
hope for an answer
espero respuesta
[Music]
[Música]
Mariel thank you very much queen
mariel muchísimas gracias reina
and we are going to talk of course about this
y vamos a hablar por supuesto sobre este
and what Xavi analyzed
y lo que xavi analizado se ha hecho
the word Dallas has become a trend today once
tendencia la palabra dallas hoy una vez
again on Twitter trending number one
más en twitter tendencia número uno
also throughout the day since last night
además durante todo el día desde anoche
okay tremendous how
vale tremendo como se había realizado
this tweet had been made okay
este tweet vale
and for it to be sad viral and it has
y para que esté triste viral y se ha
had the help of many people okay
tenido la ayuda de mucha gente vale
institutionalized because
institucionalizada porque lo ha
many people have shared it that we are going to see
compartido mucha gente que vamos a ver
in this and what I have asked everyone to
en este y lo que yo he pedido a todos
tell me who have shared the
que me pongáis quienes han compartido el
thread and I already expected it
hilo y yo ya me lo esperaba
here you are responding to me
aquí me estáis que respondiendo
and it seems very bad dear very false
y me parece muy mal querido muy falso
on your part we were talking on the
por tu parte estuvimos hablando por
phone a few months ago we buried a
teléfono hace unos meses enterramos un
bit of the fact of war but well I think I
poco la hecha de guerra pero bueno creo
remember that you told me and that you understood
recordar que me dijiste y que entendiste
the situation in Dallas not the
la situación de dallas no las
accusations that had been made false and
acusaciones que le habían hecho falsas y
so on no and that you even told me that you would
demás no y que incluso me dijiste que se
apologize to him if he asked you
disculparía con él siente lo pidiera
and now I see Elmer Studios thank you very much
y ahora veo estudios elmer muchísimas
Rey thank you very much and now you
gracias rey muchísimas gracias y ahora
have heard me it
me habéis oído
is that when someone has  he
es que cuando alguien tiene le tiene
hates him he has him and all and has something with him I do
odio lo tienen y tal y tiene algo con él
n't know
no lo sé
so you're asking people
entonces estás pidiendo a la gente que
who retweeted not here ferret that he
quien ha retwitteado no aquí hurón a que
's a streamer I haven't gone of course he
es un streamer no he ido por supuesto
will do it to me too he retweeted it he
hará que me también lo ha retwitteado no
hasn't chosen aracne
ha elegido aracne
jordi maquiavelo but let's see
jordi maquiavelo pero a ver
jordi let's see jordi let's sit down how is it that
jordi a ver jordi vamos a sentarnos como
you jordi maquiavelo have
es que tú jordi maquiavelo has
shared this tweet
compartido este tweet
yes when the cult with you the other day
si cuando el culto contigo el otro día
I let you consume whatever you
yo te dejo que me consumas lo que
want handsome blushing faces it
quieras guapo caras sonrojada es que me
gives me the creeps man why is your name core and
da mal rollo tío porque te llamas core y
listening to those messages that come from
escuchar esos mensajes que vengan de
copper the truth is regulín campos and
cobre la verdad regulín campos y
welcome
bienvenido
you are not the one who had empathy
tú no eres el que tenía empatía
jordi maquiavelo
jordi maquiavelo
let's see jordi to the other day drunk a
a ver jordi to el otro día borracho un
tweet according to you because people insulted
tuit según tú porque la gente insultó a
wish michu with your tweet and you have a lot of
wish michu con tu tweet y tienes mucha
empathy that in reality it was not like that you
empatía que en realidad no fue así lo
deleted it because wish michu ended up
borraste porque wish michu terminó por
private and 7 please remove the tweet that is
privado y 7 por favor quita el tuit que
worse like it did with me but you
peor está como hizo conmigo pero tú te
based your pants and removed it but
basaste el pantalón y lo quitaste pero
where is your empathy because I stop stop
dónde está tu empatía porque yo para
show you your hypocrisy and that you
para demostrarte tu hipocresía y que tú
have no empathy with anyone where you have
no tienes empatía con nadie donde ha
uploaded a video people let's give it a like
subido vídeo gente vamos a darle like
green heart and then we go Marc
corazón verde para luego vamos marc
when I put the tweets of the things that
cuando te puse los tuit de las cosas que
you said about giving them you told me there is
tú decías de darlas me dijiste hay
person okay because I myself said in the
persona vale porque yo mismo he dicho en
summer that we have to have empathy with
verano que hay que tener empatía con
Dallas if you see how false you are Jordi
dallas si ya ve lo falso que eres jordi
Machiavelli you are the same as the little group s you
maquiavelo eres igual que el grupito s
are exactly the same but look at
eres exactamente igual pero me mira
these things
estas cosas
this thread makes me very sorry
esto del hilo a mí me da mucha pena por
for Dallas and now because it's my
parte de dallas y ya porque es a mi
friend otherwise because [ __ ]
colega sino porque
let's see man
vamos a ver tío
or he can fall more or he can fall worse I
o puede caer mejor o puede caer peor yo
life is a person that I have a lot of
vida es una persona que le tengo mucho
appreciation for I'm not going to deny it but I recognize
aprecio no lo voy a negar pero reconozco
that he is a person who often
que es una persona que muchas veces pues
has attitudes that people do not
tiene unas actitudes que la gente no
enter and that there are people who are put
entra y que hay gente a la que le echa
off I recognize it just as I will have them
para atrás lo reconozco igual que las
just as I can be liked
tendré yo igual que yo le puedo caer
by everyone I understand that there will be
bien a todo el mundo entiendo que habrá
people who do not like me you may not like me
gente a la que le caiga mal te puede
man but that you make a
caer mal tío pero que hagáis un hilo
viral thread that becomes a trend that
viral que llegue a ser tendencia que
this girl this girl feels  super
esta chica esta chica se siente súper
proud that her mustache extends
orgullosa de que su bigote extenderse
down in fact the girl has pinned an
abajo de hecho la chica ha fijado un
incredible tweet she pinned a tweet
tweet increíble ha fijado en un tweet
bragging that she's happy that
presumiendo de que está contenta de que
look
mira
dallas is trending because of this thread that
dallas es tendencia por este hilo que
huaynos to each mayor a thread where he is being
huaynos a cada intendencia un hilo donde
pointed out
se le está señalando
of the law of the thread still but it was for being a
de la ley del hilo todavía pero era por
pedophile no because I think it is said to him
pedófilo no porque creo que se le dice
that as if his content is some kind
que como que su contenido es una especie
of pedophile group
de grupo pedófilo
6 if there is no that he is a pedophile I am not saying
6 si no hay que es un pedófilo no digo
that what bad god what
que que qué mal dios
bad guys no longer men or women
qué mal tíos ya no hombres ni mujeres
any person of any person
cualquier persona de cualquier persona
dude with a little heart who puts themselves
tío con un poco de corazón que se ponga
in the place of a kid who has already
en el lugar de un chaval que ya ha
come out innocent of everything it has been proven
salido inocente de todo es ha demostrado
that everything has been baseless accusations
que todo ha sido acusaciones sin base
that they wanted to ruin her dude put yourselves
que la han quería arruinar tío poneros
in the [ __ ] situation of sitting in a
en la situación de sentaros en un
trial
juicio
your [ __ ] head
tu cabeza
[Music]
[Música]
welcome from the thread your [ __ ] head your [ __ ]
bienvenido del hilo tu cabeza tu
head welcome thank you very much
cabeza da la bienvenida muchas
your [ __ ] head
gracias tu cabeza
those months waiting for the trial that they
esos meses esperando el juicio que te
sit you there to judge vulgar test
sientan ahí para para juzgar vulgar test
if you have done it cyberbullying hours
si tú lo has hecho ciberacoso horas
clean guys marry me innocent and yet
limpia tíos casar yo inocente y aún así
2020 end of 2020 are you trying to
2020 finales de 2020 estáis intentando
label him with an image that doesn't
tacharle de una imagen que no le
belong to him dude can you imagine it was
pertenece tío os imagináis que fuerais
you
ustedes
because you see it easy because you
porque ustedes lo veis fácil porque lo
see how it goes it's a youtube that we don't
veis cómo va es un youtube que no
know you think it's your father
conocemos pensáis que es vuestro padre
think it's your brother our
piensa que es vuestro hermano nuestro
boyfriend dude and that it's trending number one
novio tío y que es tendencia número uno
with I do
com
n't know how many retweets
no sé cuántos retweet
tens of thousands of people
decenas de miles de personas
sharing done and applauding
compartiendo hecho y aplaudiendo lo
now let's see the retweets that it says
ahora vamos a ver los retweets que pone
read this thread it is super necessary super
leer este hilo es súper necesario súper
necessary calling the pedophile it is
necesario llamar a la pedófilo
super necessary trying to destroy
es súper necesario intentar destruir la
life it is the worst thing they can accuse you of
vida es de lo peor que te pueden acusar
because they can make you go calling them an
porque te pueden hacer irlos llamándote
the hub and the email is an [ __ ] the
el hub y el email es un los
ugliest but that they call you this dude
más feos pero que te llamen esto tío
already armed they put a [ __ ]
ya de por sí armado te ponen un
comment on youtube and it already hurts you 7 it
comentario en youtube y ya te duele 7 se
falls like a knot in your heart and you are
te cae como un nudo en el corazón y te
left breathless that they call you that dude
queda sin aire que te llamen eso tío a
serve the fact god
servir al hecho dios
how much is known that no that he is innocent and
cuanto se sabe que no que es inocente y
that they have tried to go because life
que han intentado ir porque vida
how little empathy for the human being
qué poca empatía por el ser humano
you
tenéis
seriously have time it seems terrible to me it
en serio tiempo me parece fatal me
seems terrible to me
parece fatal
there each one then karma hits hard
allá cada uno luego el karma pega fuerte
karma we have already seen it here that it
el karma ya lo hemos visto aquí que
hits hard many times Jordi I finished you a
muchas veces pega fuerte jordi me acabe
fake very careful okay I
lo un falso de mucho cuidado vale me
imagined that one day you would add up in the
imaginaba que algún día sumaría en la
paw like in reality what are you
patita como en realidad de que eres
and then thank you very much
y luego muchas gracias
[Music] I
[Música]
imagined it I cacabelos empathy
me lo imaginaba yo de cacabelos empatía
you yes like you have to wear
tú sí como usted tiene que llevar
pants but the other one we are going to accuse him he
pantalón pero al otro vamos a acusarlo
answered me no way how
me ha contestado ni de coña
shameless to kill him juanito
qué poca vergüenza de matarlo juanito
saiz also retweeted it but
saiz también lo ha retwitteado pero
juanito knows I have the capture by
juanito sabe yo tengo la captura por
simón it was juanito 6 retweeted it and
simón era juanito 6 lo ha retwitteado y
then here is the retweet what a hypocrite juanito
luego aquí está el retweet que hipócrita
6 what a hypocrite you know why
juanito 6 que hipócrita sabes por qué
bonito 6 because you have been
bonito 6 porque llevas como 3 o 4 meses
uploading videos criticizing amber h for like 3 or 4 months I don't
subiendo vídeos criticando a amber h no
know how to pronounce it hello javi what there is that I do
sé cómo se pronunciará hola javi que hay
n't understand well then you're going to find
que no me entero bueno pues te vas a
out esteban thank you very much you have been
enterar esteban muchas gracias
criticizing amber for like four months handsome you know she is from your
criticando a amber es de tu canal del
[ __ ] tv channel
tv
because they have falsely accused Johnny Depp of abuse,
porque han acusado de maltrato
type criterion Juanito Safe you admitted
tipo criterio juanito safe reconociste
that he falsified a compensation he gave in
que falsifica de una compensación dio en
a live debate God your face still hasn't
un debate en directo dios todavía no se
fallen off and start
te cae la cara y ponerte a
dedicating yourself to your [ __ ]
dedicarte a tu contenido de
news content without doing these things that you
noticias sin hacer estas cosas que te
start retweeting this time you have to
pones a retuitear esto tiempo tienes que
have a face like [ __ ] cement okay
tener la cara como el cemento vale
[Music]
[Música]
Eduardo Arcos I have no [ __ ] idea that
eduardo arcos no tengo ni idea que
unfortunately two tickets weigh more than
por desgracia pesa más dos tickets que
two carts well I think that
dos carretas bueno yo creo que el odio
people's hatred the mania or I don't know other
de la gente la manía o no sé otros
factors
factores
great and Ximo this one and you have to
genial y ximo este y lo tenéis que
read it or Javi Power you have to read like
leerlo o javi power tenéis que leer como
bullying an innocent person
las en bullying a una persona inocente
how cool Abi Power put it on twitter we'll make
qué guay abi power poner en twitter ya
a video put it on twitter and
haremos un vídeo está poner en twitter y
save the screenshots Dallas
guardarme las capturas
from Abbey Power you're going to find
dallas from abbey power vais a encontrar
gold
oro
others
otras
here were isolated milestones
aquí estaban hitos aislados
and I finished what we have seen
y yo te me acabe lo que hemos visto
Cherry of course Antonia's mutual
cherry por supuesto mutual de antonia
okay I
vale
think Four Dwarves and completely safe I have to
creo que four enanos y del todo seguro
look at it but Cherry is a girl
tengo que mirarlo pero cherry es una tía
who comes from time to time to  my twitter
que viene de vez en cuando a mi twitter
to mess with me okay
a meterse conmigo vale
mutual actor already follows with Antonio I
mutual de actor ya se sigue con antonio
know it oscillates I think it's a colleague device I do
sé que oscila creo que es colega device
n't know who Eduardo Arcos is Antonia
no sé quién es eduardo arcos
Mieres's mother has followed me
antonia la madre de mieres ha seguido me
they told me that David Bravo too I don't know
han dicho que david bravo también no sé
if it's true lie hasn't seen a
si será verdad mentira no ha visto
screenshot but Antonia this is what
captura pero antonia esto siempre ha
a lot of people have always said via email that Antonia
dicho mucha gente por email que antonia
has followed this girl man I
ha seguido a esta chica tío
mean I'm really freaking out at least
o sea flipo de verdad por lo menos
Antonia hide these things
antonia ocultar estas cosas
whatever you have with Dallas that you do
que tengáis lo que tengáis con el dallas
n't turn the pages
que no pasáis páginas
okay but at least hide these
vale pero por lo menos ocultar estas
things guys I
cosas tíos
mean this is the criteria to start
o sea este es el criterio para empezar a
following someone you don't know I don't
seguir a alguien que no conoces
know who this is
no sé quién es esta
for Fabia of course then they'll make a
para de fabia por supuesto luego harán
phobia he doesn't want me to say anything last
fobia no quiere que le diga nada último
but he deserves it he's much more handsome
pero que merece es mucho más guapo
thanks blue heart grace Mariel
gracias corazón azul gracia mariel
thank you very much
muchísimas gracias
for Negro he doesn't want us to say anything
para negro no quiere que le digamos nada
poor
pobrecita
bitter Miller
amarga miller
to Mark Miller this thread is very necessary
a mark miller este hilo es muy necesario
very necessary to love Havana very
muy necesario que amar la habana muy
necessary is to learn to walk learn to
necesario es aprender a andar aprender a
read
leer
eat vegetables
comer verduras
but it's very necessary that
pero es muy necesario que acusen a
Dallas be accused of  pedophile I do
dallas de pedófilo
n't know I find it strange that
no sé me resulta raro que
this thread is to once again publicly
ese hilo es para de nuevo públicamente
destroy Dallas' image accusing him
destrozar la imagen de dallas acusándolo
of going after his livelihood you just have to see
de ir a por su sustento sólo hay que ver
who is sharing it the same
quién es el que lo comparte el mismo
group is of efforts that are terrible it is
grupo es de esfuerzos que están fatal lo
shared by the same group as always I don't know
comparte el mismo grupo de siempre no sé
why it is bitter criticized and because she is
por qué amarga criticada y porque está
upset the relationship occurs given the content with
molesta se da la relación dada la con
sexual content I will
contenido sexual
not do what does not embitter her literally
no haré lo que no le amarga literalmente
your content was sexual he
tu contenido era sexual
was dedicated to that although there is the genius
se dedicaba a eso aunque está el genio
of speculating and it has been to save me to
de especular y ha sido a sálvame a
talk to talk about sanse or not embitter
hablar a hablar de sanse o no amargar
the criticism I do not understand I do not understand
las críticas no lo entiendo no entiendo
but it is very necessary in fact the girl
pero es muy necesario de hecho la chica
who made the thread is still there go to us and if she
que hizo el hilo sigue ahí vaya nos y si
also follows David Bravo
también sigue a david bravo
yes but one thing that she continues and others
sí pero una cosa que ella siga y otras
that they follow her because she can
que les sigan a ella porque ella puede
follow whoever but the strong ones that
seguir a quien sea pero los fuertes que
follow her back simply
le sigan a ella de vuelta simplemente
because of this I do not know how to
por esto no sé
see the light seeing them has followed see those that I
ver luz verlos le ha seguido ver los que
had the problem with dallas
tuve el problema con dallas
ingrid to continue I freak out with an individual I
ingrid a seguir flipo con un individuo
freak out with ingrid
flipo con ingrid
the bird
el ave
isaac man how pathetic  ereixas corrales
isaac tío qué patético ereixas corrales
I
yo
this that is there for obsession to win
esto que es haya por obsesión por ganar
a few retweets because yes he doesn't
unos retweet porque sí no
have 3 16 but he seems to me one of the
tiene 3 16 a pero me parece de las
most pathetic people there is on the
personas más patéticas que hay en la red
social network is uncle sales debate with me and
social es tío ventas debate conmigo y
watermelon and we talk because we have many
sandía y hablamos que tenemos muchas
things to talk about topics that a folder
cosas que hablar temas que una carpeta
about your things well you already have
sobre cosas tuyas bueno tú ya ya hay
colleagues of yours who are also going to
colegas tuyos que también se van a
take a kingdom let's see soon you are worth of the little
llevar un reino a ver pronto vales del
group and of your verified tweeters
grupito y de tu tuiteros verificado
white already at six some things that are
white ya a seis unas cosas que son
worthy of giving a moral class to
dignas de darle clase de moral a la
worthy people and in history boast about
gente digna y en historia presumir de
something well I will tell but he seems to me the
una cosa bueno ya contaré pero me parece
most pathetic of the maipo screams and
de lo más patético del maipo grita y
sad that something
triste que algo
[Music]
[Música]
what a surprise no what a
qué sorpresa no
surprise
qué sorpresa
this ultra curated thread deserves to be
esta ultra curada de hilo merece ser
read at least once at least if you
leída como mínimo una vez como mínimo si
can waste all day reading the
podéis perder todo el día leyendo lo
best
mejor
Felipe
felipe
mother or Felipe if you are the saddest thing there is
madre o felipe si tú eres lo más triste
on YouTube there is a video about
que hay en youtube hay un vídeo sobre
Felipe where I put all the harassment that he
felipe donde pongo todo el acoso que él
has done to Dallas and there you can see what
ha hecho a dallas y ahí podéis ver qué
kind of characters
tipo de personajes
ingrid
ingrid
you are  watching thanks to the people who have
estáis viendo gracias a la gente que ha
made it so that I am using Abidal
hecho que esté utilizar abidal
Bliss and of course how could it be missing it couldn't
bliss y claro como podía faltar no pudo
fail there is no
fallar
lack not one will be hormone also
no falta ni uno estará hormona también
Luiz in Derá
luiz en derá
I imagine because let's see I have been I do
yo me imagino porque a ver yo he estado
not confirm it I do not confirm it but I
no lo confirmo no lo confirmó pero yo me
imagine that this is the thread they will have
imagino que esto es el hilo se lo habrán
passed it on by tweet by whatsapp
pasado por por tweet por whatsapp
please let's share this that he
por favor vamos a compartir esto que él
throws [ __ ] Dallas because I have been
tira dallas porque yo he estado
on this side and I know what you do not
en este bando y sé lo que haces no
urgent it was uncle we
urgente era tío
give everyone a retweet to see if he
le damos a todos retweet a ver si nos
denounces us all he is still waiting for you to
denuncia a todos todavía está esperando
report him and sell that you are going to
tu denunciarlo y vender a que tú me va a
report me to report he had already
denunciar a denunciar ya me había
reported me they send me
denunciado me mandan
but well when the time comes
pero bueno cuando llegue el momento
we will talk about the conversation I had
hablaremos de la conversación que tuve
with title and the whole thing no longer by burofax that
con título y entera ya no de burofax que
everyone knows but about the
lo sabe todo el mundo sino de la
conversation of what you told me in
conversación de lo que me dijiste por
private that someone had reported me had
privado de que me había denunciado una
filed an
me había puesto una querella
unofficial complaint against me as if they didn't exist
extraoficial como si no existieran
or it's terrible that Dallas says that it is going to
o sea terrible que dallas diga que va a
report someone but you tell
denunciar a alguien pero tú me dices a
me that you are going to  report in July of
mí que me vas a denunciar en julio del
last year that he was going to report me for
año pasado que me iba a denunciar por
things that you yourself had told me
cosas que tú mismo me habías dicho a mí
too but well very well
también pero bueno muy bien
this one doesn't have
este no se tiene
javi power
javi power
big again
grande de nuevo
jealousy
celos
ingrid again
ingrid de nuevo
maybe and she is tremendous it
quizás y está tremendo
's a friend that salt
es colega de que sal
someone is missing here missing crown
falta alguien aquí falta corona
millions of green leaves I
millones de hojas verdes
uploaded it boom and wow it's thalía from this I have
la subí boom y guau es thalía de este
here an interview that they
tengo aquí una entrevista que le
did that we have to react the
hicieron que tenemos que reaccionar el
day that there is no salsero remind me that
día que no haya salsero recordarme que
we react to the interview of
reaccionemos a la entrevista de
interview that I have saved this girl is
entrevista que tengo guardada esta chica
worth millions of thanks
vale millones de gracias
for this thread thanks
por este hilo
thanks her
le da las gracias
in her life this is to thank
en su vida esto es agradecer
my people were at full capacity withdrawing all the
mi gente era a tope retirando todo el
power that retweets her
poder que le retuitea
technically this is not a shared
técnicamente esto no es un compartido
that david bravo
que david bravo
doubled it to a tweet from the girl well I
la doble a un tuit de la chica bueno me
imagine it will have been because the girl
imagino que habrá sido porque la chica
will be afraid of being reported and
tendrá miedo de que la denuncia y se
wants advice well I'm not going to get into that
quiere asesorar bueno no voy a meter en
forces have given him light
fuerzas le ha dado light
forms that we
formas
were watching a video of his
el que estuvimos viendo un vídeo suyo
two days ago on place tves
hace dos días en place tves de
Spanish television that you have it on the
televisión española que lo tenéis en el
secondary channel
canal secundario
in which he canceled he said that
en el que él cancelaba decía que había
the culture of  the
que cancelar a la cultura de la
cancellation when it was false
cancelación cuando era falsa
how false I am
qué falso soy yo
how false you are dude
qué falso sois tío
this is followers
a esto es followers
follower is that they follow her no
follower es que las siguen a ella no
and force gave her line that false for
y fuerza le dio line que falso for
fashion or I mean to you guys
fashion o sea a ustedes
I have a little investigating directly this is
tengo un poco de investigando directo
this is the criteria of things
está este es el criterio de las cosas
like for example what we just
como por ejemplo lo que acabamos de
talked about when they talk about the
hablar de forma cuando hablan de la
cancel culture or look when they
cultura de la cancelación o mira cuando
talk about this it is fair and this can be
hablan de esto es justo y esto se puede
done and this is not they are not fair dude it is
hacer y esto no no son justos tío se
based on the fact that they are people on my side in
basa que son personas de mi bando en
our staff on my side, I am there
nuestro personal de mi bando ya está yo
for example if I see that they do an
por ejemplo si yo veo que le hacen una
injustice to him I will do it I say it here I mean
injusticia me haré yo lo digo aquí
I criticized he is believed in because he
o sea yo critiqué a se cree en él porque
made a video against my bird and
hizo un vídeo en contra de mi ave y la
called her something that did not seem wrong to me
llamó cosa que a mí no me parecía
and I get along with he is
incorrecta y yo me llevo bien con se
believed and it is convenient bad
cree y conviene mal
but they do not this is dependencies to
pero ellos no ello es dependencias a
give to everything that is thanks to another
darle a todo lo que sea gracias a otro
please have empathy I do not know what
por favor tener empatía no sé qué
rooster
gallo
damage does to the people that come out one of
daño le da la geste de que sal una de
the good things that the coronavirus has achieved
las cosas buenas que ha conseguido el
is that at least since 2020
coronavirus es que por lo menos de 2020
the 7  happy
se han acabado los 7 diarios de feliz
monday diaries [ __ ] like that because nobody is
lunes así porque ya nadie es
happy anymore but since nobody is happy then
feliz pero como ya nadie es feliz pues
what an obsession
qué obsesión
indal and see thank you very much for your
indal y ver muchas gracias por tu
donation
donación
javi I don't know if you know but david bravo
javi no sé si lo sabe pero david bravo
was initially a showman on a program
inicialmente era showman de un programa
[Music]
[Música]
austria there is another message to me dude not from
austria se me hay otro mensaje tío no de
a dani mateo program
un programa de dani mateo
well not as a showman I don't know if I
bueno tanto como showman no sé si yo se
could call myself a showman but I know he
podría calificar showman pero yo sé que
was a guest because there are videos on
iba de invitado porque están vídeos en
youtube in fact or here thank you very much
youtube de hecho o aquí muchas gracias
watch it and thanks to you he only tells you
verlo y gracias a usted se cuenta solo
[ __ ] it's how nerve you
es que qué cara tan dura tienen
all have dude I mean
todos tío
for fun he gave her a follow
o sea que for fun le ha dado follow
[ __ ] unleash her we mentioned her in the
perra desata la mencionamos en el vídeo
kfc video because kfc was following this account they're
de kfc por que kfc seguía esta cuenta
going to fly
que van a volar
charo be very careful okay I'm glad it's
charo de mucho cuidado vale me alegro de
finished
que se haya finalizado
but if you want less there's much less
pero si quiere que menos hay mucho menos
progress I
progreso
'll play he says it wouldn't be slander
tocaré dice que no sería una calumnia
well slander but it could be a
bueno una calumnia pero podría ser una
fault I've read it and he'll do it less is it
falta lo he leído él y lo hará menos le
worth it to
vale
me it seems to me it
me parece
seems heavy
me parece heavy
and well and here I repeat myself
y bueno y aquí se repite
about machiavelli
yo lo de maquiavelo
but someone had sent me that
pero alguien me había mandado que
hormones also
hormonas también
someone me  I had sent that gorgona
alguien me había mandado que gorgona
also no I don't believe that orgone is missing
también no no me creo yo que falte orgón
here at this meeting that can't be
aquí en esta quedada eso no puede ser
that is I don't believe it,
eso es no me lo creo yo
gorgona, I wouldn't swear that
gorgona no juraría que más mandaba
gorgona was in charge retweeting I
gorgona retuiteando
don't know what there is here is the retweet so as
no sé que hay aquí está el retweet para
not to appear on the live
no salir en el directo
Dallas and you are friends again or vice
dallas y tú volvéis a ser amigos o vice
and worse of course
y peor claro
when not tell me what medal and edit what you
cuando no dime de qué presea y edite de
lack is like that
que careces es así
Antonio thank you very much let's see let's
antonio a muchas gracias a ver vamos a
read first
leer primero
today we have here bring time with this
hoy tenemos aquí trae tiempo con esto
let's read the first one who said
vamos a leer el primero que ha dicho
also aires
además también aires
the grace will give them when she can no longer
la gracia las dará cuando no pueda
practice for a court when they
volver a ejercer para un juzgado cuando
condemn you with the complaint that will
te condenen con la denuncia que te
come to you and the sentence that the
llegará y la condena que te caerá el
judge will give you to this girl there was a law or for the one that
juez a esta chica había ley o por el que
the psychologists
las psicólogas
abi power who paints her with dallas
abi power que pinta a ella con dallas
that I missed well to my power she is very
que me perdí bueno a mi power es muy
close to focusing sea focusing is missing
amiga de focusing sea focusing falta
rodger also weligton
rodger también weligton
thanks to the pib it
gracias al pib
is that effectively she will not be able to declare a
es que efectivamente no podrá declarar
record for this for sure and I
antecedentes por esto seguro y me
will make sure that it is known who she is my
aseguraré de que se sepa quién es mi
experience does not have insurance that ends  of
experiencia no tiene seguro que acaba de
leaving the race if she has even
salir de la carrera si es que siquiera
finished those who do this if they
ha terminado quienes hacen esto si los
are university students important credits
son universitarios créditos importantes
hello thanks for your interest
hola gracias por tu interés
in fact this is the first course in which I
de hecho este es el primer curso en el
work as a university professor
que ejerció como docente universitaria
other careers and two masters there is nothing
otras carreras y dos máster no hay nada
to report since you have not taken
que denunciar puesto que no te has
any courses I limit myself to exposing the
cursos de nada me limitó a exponer los
problems of your content I understand
problemáticos de tu contenido entiendo
that you dislike it bye also you
que te desagrada chau
are also a lawyer and bodies what I
además también eres abogada y cuerpos lo
see now she says sarcastically no I
que veo ahora dice sarcásticamente no o
mean it is not that she is literally a lawyer but she
sea no es que literal sea abogada sino
is saying it closely
que lo está diciendo con cerca
the guy sura followed this chick
el tío sura seguida esta pava
just started working as a teacher
acaba de empezar a ejercer de profesora
andrade when we find out at your
andrade cuando descubramos en tu
university this one is going to make them laugh a lot she
universidad ésta les va a hacer muchas
had a teacher with a criminal
gracias tenía una profesora con
record
antecedentes
now after him and we read it from the thread
ahora después de él y lo leemos del hilo
of helado who told me that the
de helada que me ha dicho que la
dismantled
desmontada
anyway
en fin
love her my injury
amarla mi lesión
the truth that they tell us the recent and
la verdad que nos cuentan el reciente y
ridiculous promoted by my ex his mother
lo ridículo promovido por mi ex su madre
and his friends
y sus amigos
this is not a lie okay we have already seen
esto no es mentira vale lo hemos visto
what
ya qué
this group of people is these people for
está este grupo de gente esta gente por
well it is nothing new they have made
bueno no es nada nuevo han hecho que se
the tweet end okay
finalice el tweet vale
where they call me everything basically it is
donde me llaman de todo básicamente es
their way of  get even because this year he filed
su forma de desquitarse porque este año
another complaint against me
me volvió a meter otra denuncia más
and they have archived it
y se la han vuelto a archivar otra vez
again so to sum up
más así resumiendo
[Music]
[Música]
Noelia thank you very much yes I have already done it I
noelia muchas gracias sí ya yo he hecho
knew it but I couldn't say
lo sabía pero no lo podría decir
send and tried to reopen the case to
enviar e intentó volver a abrir el caso
tried to report Dallas again
para intentó volver a denunciar a dallas
for the same thing as always they told him
por lo mismo de siempre le dijeron por
please see you later now really yes yes
favor que hasta luego ya de verdad sí sí
yes they told him see you later I
sí le dijeron que hasta luego
imagine he still shows his face
me imagino que da la cara aún
a video about the fact it seems incredible to me
un vídeo sobre hecho me parece increíble
that still in 2020 I am trying
que todavía en 2020 estoy en intentarlo
because I am trying by force to get him
por estar intentando por que le
convicted I mean
condenen
I do
o sea yo ya
n't understand it anymore really there are
no lo entiendo de verdad
things that I don't understand okay
hay cosas que no entiendo vale
but oh well I'll leave it there give him something he
pero bueno ahí lo dejo darle algo ha
said I knew it but oh well he has already
contado yo lo sabía pero bueno ya le ha
told him he filed another complaint against him
contado le volvió a meter otra denuncia
and they have archived it again there I
y se le han vuelto a archivar ahí lo
leave it aside well let's move on I think
dejo aparte bueno a pasar las cosas creo
giving them here he says it I bet I
que darlas por aquí lo dice
challenge the debate agent nobody is in the
apuesto a retar al debate agente nadie
debate how strange
estar debate qué raro
hello javi yesterday I became a member yesterday to
hola javi ayer me hice miembro para
support you I love your content I hope you had
apoyarte me encanta tu contenido espero
a good day thank you very much
hayas tenido un buen día muchas gracias
maxxi a huge hug summary of the  ct
el maxxi un abrazo enorme resumen del ct
from dallas a college student who just
de dallas una universitaria que acaba de
finished her degree and with
terminar la carrera y con ser
experience pretends to be an expert on an
experiencia finge ser una experta de una
experience lie and phrase authority
experiencia mentira y frase autoridad
to do a psychoanalysis on me where she
para hacerme un psicoanálisis donde me
treats me like a jerk
trata de pedo
and my ex is her mother and I've been dating him
y mi ex su madre y lo salía desde
forever they give him the dt
siempre le dan el dt
by the way no psychologist so-
por cierto ningún psicólogo entre
called serious would ever do a
comillas serio jamás haría un
psychoanalysis on a person they've
psicoanálisis a una persona con la que
never had dealings with
no ha tenido trato
and says they're going to make videos about this
y dice que va a sacar vídeos sobre esto
we'll react
reaccionaremos
here alienated she says the same thing agrees at
aquí alienada dice lo mismo coincide al
first the lynching in dallas is
principio el linchamiento a dallas es
constant and it doesn't matter how many times
constante y da igual cuántas veces se
his innocence is proven it must be
pruebe su inocencia tiene que ser
unbearable a lot of encouragement and strength it would
insoportable mucho ánimo y fuerza a mí
seem incredible to me
me parecería increíble
sanz a lot of time goes by no this
sanz pasa a pasar mucho tiempo no esto
would have to be flames that overcomes it or not that
tendría que estar llamas que supera o no
this one is innocent that he has you he has
que éste tiene inocente que te tiene ha
done those things that may fall for better or
hecho esas cosas que pueden caer mejor o
worse but it's not those things me well
peor pero que no es esas cosas yo pues
nothing god that
nada dios
by balls they want to ruin life
que por quieren arruinar la vida
and here's the good part
y aquí está lo bueno
guess I'm going to drink some water
adivinad voy a beber un poco de agua
while people I'm going to drink
mientras que la gente te voy a beber un
some water
poco de agua
five hours here live
cinco horas aquí en directo
guess who just had a
adivine a quien acaba de tener una
firm conviction to pay me 40 thousand  euros plus
condena firme a pagarme 40 mil euros más
costs for the nonsense he dedicated to
costas por las burradas que se dedicó a
saying about me in a video that has already been deleted
decir sobre mí en un vídeo ya borrado
for so many videos revealing how calm he
por tanto vídeo desvelando lo tranquilo
hasn't said that we'll see, we'll see. Here
no ha dicho que veremos veremos aquí
what I would like to know was born is no longer
lo que me gustaría saber ya no es de
who it is about what
quién se trata
I would like to know
lo que me gustaría saber
an already deleted video is to stay with that
un vídeo ya borrado es quedarnos con eso
whoever the video is deleted what I would
sea quien sea borrado el vídeo lo que me
like to know we
gustaría saber
will see this in the facua news
veremos esto en las noticias de facua
because this would already be a conviction this is not
porque esto ya sería una condena esto no
that they have reported and they ask for so much I have
es que han denunciado y le piden tanto
made a conviction
he hecho una condena
this will come out in facua facua releases
esto saldrá en facua de facua saca
news about when they report a youtuber
noticias de cuando denuncian a youtuber
and things like that
y cosas así
or not
o no
this news makes the media happy and
estas noticias nos alegran los medios y
well it's
bueno está
good because we'll find out
bueno pues ya nos enteraremos
we'll find out when dallas that the
nos enteraremos cuando dallas a que el
video
vídeo
let's read the thread okay to know what it says I have
vamos a leer el hilo vale saber qué pone
n't read it I promise I've been out there all
no lo he leído lo prometo estado todo el
day after starting directly
día por ahí después de empezar directo
with Roma you already know
con roma ya lo sabéis
the grooming for social on youtube and gives
el grooming para social en youtube y da
the review this youtuber has already been
la review este youtuber ya ha sido
pointed out for several months as problematic
señalado varias meses como problemático
but until now I have not seen an analysis
pero hasta ahora no he visto un análisis
of his content from this perspective
de su contenido desde esta perspectiva
so I have spent a few days watching
así que me he pasado unos días viendo
many of his videos  to do it right
muchos de sus vídeos para hacerlo bien
here
aquí
here we are going to take into account the context
aquí vamos a tener en cuenta el contexto
of things let's see they just sent me
de las cosas a ver me acaban de mandar
an email 19 look who else has
un email 19 mira quién más lo ha
shared it let's see who I missed
compartido a ver quién se me escapa
who do you think it will be let's see
quién creéis que será a ver
[Laughter]
[Risas]
ha ha ha ha ha ha I
ja ja ja ja ja ja
can't say because you don't know who it is
no puedo decirlo porque no sabéis quién
no well nothing an ally
es no pues nada un aliado
[Music]
[Música]
to the me to the ones of Ivan
a las me a las de iván
it is him
es a él
in the context of the thing it is serious
en el contexto de la cosa es seria
[Music]
[Música]
Dallas has already been pointed out as being a
dallas ya ha sido señalado de ser una
problematic person and so seriously to the
persona problemática y tan en serio al
longing doubts Dalai like that or has it been given to
anhelo dudas dalai así o se ha dado de
be a problematic person
ser una persona problemática
what are we referring to because if
a qué nos estamos refiriendo porque si
the title is grooming
el título es el grooming
when you are making reference to the
cuando estás haciendo referencia a las
controversies and the problems that surround
polémicas y la problemática que rodea
giving I don't think you are referring to if
dar no creo que te esté refiriendo a si
Congress is discussed it is discussed with Ibai he
se discute congreso se discute con ibai
is pointing out the times that they have
está señalando las veces que lo han
pointed him out the media already comes out for his
señalado ya salen los medios por sus
problems not accusations of abuse
problemas no acusaciones de maltrato
accusations of pedophilia at least I
acusaciones de pedofilia yo por lo menos
understand it that way
lo entiendo así
I at least understand it that way
yo por lo menos lo entiendo así
in this context but well let's
en este contexto pero bueno vamos a
continue first of all what is grooming it
seguir antes de nada que es el grooming
is the process  often via online
es el proceso muchas veces vía online
through which an adult establishes
mediante el cual un adulto establece
contact with a child or adolescent,
contacto con un niño niña o adolescente
gradually gaining their trust to
ganándose poco a poco su confianza para
sexually abuse the minor. Okay, that is,
abusar sexualmente del menor vale osea
contact between an adult and a minor
el contacto de un adulto con un menor
to gain their trust in order to
para ganarse su confianza para abusar
sexually abuse them. The process can be
sexualmente de él el proceso puede
divided into four points, try to
dividirse en cuatro puntos intenten
remember them because they are important. The
recordarlos porque son importantes en el
rest of the thread is going to be long. Adult
resto del hilo va a ser largo el adulto
one selects a vulnerable victim. 2. Makes
uno selecciona una víctima vulnerable 2
sure to have access to said
se asegura de tener acceso a dicha
victim. 3. Begins to develop a
víctima 3 empieza a desarrollar un
bond of trust. To do this, offers
vínculo de confianza para ello ofrece
help, shares intimate experiences,
ayuda comparte experiencias íntimas se
shows himself as a mentor, role model, and
muestra como un mentor modelo a seguir y
tries to keep the victim away from her family. 4. Raising
trata de alejarla de su familia
awareness about
la s la de sensibilizar ante contenido
sexual content. Strategies for number 4 are
sexual las estrategias para el 4 se
divided into communication and
dividen en comunicación de de
awareness-raising. Conversations are carried out by
sensibilizadora se realizando las
showing pornography
conversaciones mostrando pornografía a
through games and jokes
través de juegos y bromas
and reformulation. Interfering with the
y reformulación interferir en la
victim's sexuality by conveying
sexualidad de la víctima transmitiendo
that sex will be beneficial for her.
que el sexo será beneficioso para ella
Several studies have shown that
varios estudios han mostrado que
detecting this process and differentiating it from
detectar este proceso y diferenciarlo de
a normal child-adult interaction is
una interacción normal niño adulto es
very difficult, both on the part of other
muy difícil tanto por parte de otros
adults and the victim. This is why
adultos como de la víctima con lo que
many predatory behaviors go
muchos comportamientos predatorios pasan
unnoticed. What is a
desapercibidos qué es una relación para
social relationship in a unilateral relationship?
social en la relación unilateral
symbolic between characters spectator
simbólica entre personajes espectador
arises from the emotions
surge a partir de las emociones
thoughts and attitudes that the
pensamientos y actitudes que el
spectator experiences in relation
espectador a experimentar en relación
to an actor people on youtube
con un actor personas en youtube
discomfort you would have and that relationship
malestar ustedes tendría y esa relación
with a youtuber no you know the
con un youtuber no ustedes conocéis al
youtuber or had a relationship with him
youtube ni tenía una relación con él
many times you maybe have
muchas veces ustedes a lo mejor me
affection for me you trust me and
tenéis cariño me tenéis confianza y a
many I don't know I know some
muchos yo no conozco conozco algunos
like the logical one it's not worth it it refers to that
como el lógico no vale se refiere a esa
feeling of friendship and familiarity that
sensación de amistad y familiaridad que
the spectator develops if the youtube is the one they
el espectador desarrolla si el youtube
see as trustworthy in
el que ve como digno de confianza en
children
niños
bps they relate to learning
bps se relacionan con el aprendizaje
connection brum in
connection brum en relaciones para
social relationships grooming refers to
sociales el grooming hace referencia a
an adult selecting a
un adulto seleccionando a una víctima
specific victim with whom they deploy their
concreta con la que despliega sus
strategies is there a way for
estrategias hay manera de que el
grooming and social relationships to
grooming y las relaciones para sociales
act at the same time for that we need to talk
actúen a la vez para eso necesita hablar
about these youtubers that I don't know their
sobre este youtubers que no conozco sus
casuals but apparently he is a youtuber
casuales pero al parecer es un youtuber
that well has had a move Aaron
que bueno que ha tenido una movida aaron
until June was one of the biggest youtubers from
hasta junio era uno de los youtubers más
his audience came from girls
grandes de provenido su audiencia niñas
and preadolescents after a controversy they
y preadolescentes tras una polémica
refloated videos from his channel in which
reflotaron vídeos de su canal en los que
among other things the
entre otras cosas sobresalía el
sexual content in code stood out  humor
contenido sexual en clave de humor
aimed at children well we would have to see the
dirigido a niños bueno habría que ver el
content if it was aimed at children or not
contenido si iba dirigido a niños o no
because there is going to be it is aimed at children
porque va a haber va dirigido a niños
because you missed the kit face upside down face upside down face
porque te faltó el kit de cara al revés
smiling with
cara al revés cara sonriendo con los
eyes closed face smiling with
ojos cerrados cara sonriendo con los
eyes closed did not beat I have not missed
ojos cerrados no batía no me ha faltado
that now smiling with eyes
que ahora sonriendo con los ojos para
up open because no we have not
arriba abiertos porque no no lo hemos
said the kilo
dicho el kilo
a video in which he did
un vídeo en el que hacía
or no video in which he asked his
o ningún vídeo en el que hacía a su
12 year old cousin
prima de 12 años preguntas de tipo
sexual questions and another in which he simulated
sexual y otro en el que simulaba
masturbating in front of an image of willow
masturbarse ante una imagen de willow
smith the smith family tweeted about this
smith la familia smith tuiteó sobre esto
and for now it seems that his career is
y por ahora parece ser que su carrera ha
over
terminado
[Music]
[Música]
nahuel thank you very much welcome to rey
nahuel muchas gracias' bienvenido a rey
the serious one did this
el serio hizo esto
simulated such with the image of huilo
simulaba tal con la imagen de huilo
huilo in the daughter of double edge
huilo en la hija de doble filo
this type of content could constitute
este tipo de contenido podría constituir
a group for social
en un grupo para social
term that I take
término que tomo
from this video
de este vídeo
several testimonies have emerged from girls
han surgido varios testimonios de chicas
who grew up watching elche's content
que crecieron viendo el contenido de
and who tell how it made them
elche y que cuentan cómo les hizo
normalize behavior of sal izado
normalizar comportamiento de sal izado
bla bla
bla bla
well here he is talking about the case of
bueno aquí está hablando del caso de
this type
este tipo
if the fans want to continue belonging to the in
si los fans quieren seguir perteneciendo
two groups  for visits then you
al en dos grupos para visitas entonces
must agree with him
debes de estar de acuerdo con él de lo
otherwise they will not be intelligent or
contrario no serán inteligentes ni
mature
maduros
being expelled alex or group
siendo expulsados álex o grupo
in terms of his personal relationship with
en cuanto a su relación personal con
fans shares his feelings and
fans comparte sus sentimientos y
vulnerabilities with them
vulnerabilidades con ellos
[Music]
[Música]
pedro welcome pedro defines himself as
pedro bienvenido pedro se define como
a person very willing to help them and
una persona muy dispuesta a ayudarlos y
listen if they have problems he gives them
escuchar si tienen problemas les da
advice and sets himself as an example see
consejo y se pone como ejemplo a ver
this tweet I think that any youtube
este tuit yo creo que cualquier youtube
on more than one occasion has expressed
en más de una ocasión ha expresado
personal experiences of their own so
experiencias personales suyas para
that you have my experience
para que ustedes tengan mi experiencia
as an example or not and the issue of listening
como ejemplo o no y el tema de escuchar
and giving advice well it is assumed that
y dar consejos bueno se supone que a
through the youtube channel I would
través del canal de youtube vería
personally see with each follower I think that
personalmente con cada seguidor eso creo
almost no youtuber does that not at
que no lo hace casi ningún youtuber no
most in live shows not with those who
como mucho en los directos no con los
are live I don't know
que estén en directos no sé
in the video the parents who hated their
en el vídeo los padres que odiaban a sus
children I do
hijos
n't know who is the worst of all of them
ya no sé quién es peor de todos ellos
face vomiting
cara vomitando
in the video the parents who hated their
en el vídeo los padres que odiaban a sus
children to severe the audience that their
hijos a severas la audiencia que sus
parents do not value them that they mistreat them
padres no les valoran que les maltratan
and that they do and that he does know how to see what they
y que a él sí y que él si sabe ver lo
suffer in these images the grain
que sufren en estas imágenes lo de grano
then the transcribed video makes it very
entonces el vídeo transcrito deja muy
clear that it does not include  all the parents
claro que no incluye a todos los padres
answers here already
respuestas aquí ya
with the first sentence I think that it no longer makes it
con la primera frase yo creo que ya no
clear to all of its followers that
hace ver a todos sus seguidores que su
its parents hate them it will not refer
que sus padres les odian no se referirá
to parents who treat their children badly I
a padres que traten mal a sus hijos me
imagine not seen that video but
imagino no visto ese vídeo pero por
unfortunately so to a great majority
desgracia así a una gran mayoría
if in your case you have a
si en tu caso tienes una familia
perfect family one for the perfect of tastes
perfecta uno para el perfecto de gustos
I want you to know that you are
quiero que sepas que eres un
privileged and very lucky to
privilegiado y tiene mucha suerte de
have a family like that the truth is that
tener una familia así lo cierto es que
the majority of parents are a failure as
la mayoría de padres son un fracaso como
people as educators nobody has a
personas como educadores nadie tiene una
perfect family with which its audience is
familia perfecta con lo que su audiencia
not going to identify with that section
no se va a identificar con esa sección
and will understand that the video is directed
y entenderá que el vídeo se dirige
well to see
bueno a ver
[Music] I do
[Música]
not agree with this with this
no estoy de acuerdo con esta con esta
statement of the video because nobody is
afirmación del vídeo porque nadie somos
perfect and nobody is born knowing okay in
perfectos y nadie nace sabiendo vale de
fact it is not the same experience of
hecho no es la misma experiencia de
educating and raising your first child as the
educar y criar a tu primer hijo que al
second okay because the experience is little
segundo vale porque poco es la
Javi I love you Javi I love you you are handsome but
javi te amo javi te amo eres guapo pero
no more than me well I do not doubt it Axel
no más que yo bueno no lo dudo axel
after the last video I have received
después del último vídeo he recibido
many stories of children who are unhappy
muchas historias de hijos descontentos
with their parents he is close and
con sus padres se muestra cercano y
accessible to listen to the story of his
accesible a escuchar la historia de su
fan yes  They understand
fan el si les entiende
that it leads a person to have children
que lleva a una persona a tener hijos
the reasons are purely biological
los motivos son puramente biológicos
so that the species continues well
para que la especie continúe bueno
purely biological no
puramente biológico no
the reasons are many illusions because
los motivos son muchos ilusiones porque
you like children many reasons
te gusten los niños muchísimos motivos
love
el amor
having I see it as an experience
el tener yo veo una experiencia
that you share with your partner when there is
que compartes con tu pareja cuando hay
love very beautiful because it is something that you
amor muy bonitas porque es algo que
have created between the two of you it is incredible to
habéis creado entre los dos es increíble
have children I recommend it
tener hijos os lo recomiendo
when you have I recommend it but if you
cuando tengáis lo recomiendo pero si
are young
sois jóvenes
plan to have them now when you are the
en plan tenerlos ahora cuando tengáis la
age that I am now okay with 35 or 40
edad que tengo yo ahora vale con 35 o 40
years old
años
stopped traveling going out doing
a apartaron de viajar de salir de hacer
everything your partner for many years and there is
de todo vuestra pareja muchos años y hay
time for everything then having children
tiempo para todo luego tener hijos
whatever the thoughts that go through
sea como sea los pensamientos que pasan
their head are the same when you
por su cabeza son los mismos cuando
adopt a new pet
adoptas una mascota nueva
water no way
agua ni de coña
coria
de coria
how to do it right having a child with
cómo hacerlo bien tener un hijo con
pets yes it is nice to adopt a
mascotas si es bonito adoptar una
pet yes of course but it is not comparable to
mascota sí claro pero no es comparable a
a creation blood of your blood okay so
una creación sangre de tu sangre vale
whoever it is wherever you are
así que sea quien sea estés donde estés
if your parents have already had you and
si tus padres ya han tenido y te han
raised you it has basically been their pet
criado ha sido básicamente su mascota
wow
wow
for many years it has been their
durante muchos años ha sido su perrito
lapdog
faldero
wow this fact this video is from the same
wow este hecho este vídeo es de la misma
but it will have  a lot of years in
sino que tendrá un mogollón de años en
plan
plan
and will not agree now with these
y no estará de acuerdo ahora con estas
statements
afirmaciones
and only have children to live through
y sólo tienen hijos para vivir a través
them what they have always wanted to be
de ellos lo que siempre han querido ser
in this yes there are many parents who are
en esto sí que hay muchos padres que son
like that
así
in this of 2014
en esto de 2014
the video is worth great in this yes there are
el vídeo vale genial en esto sí que hay
many parents who have a life that they have
muchos padres que tienen una vida que
been the fruit that are frustrated with
han sido fruto que están frustradas con
their lives because they have wanted to be something
sus vidas porque han querido ser algo
that they have not achieved, they have not managed to
que no han conseguido no ha conseguido
be completely happy and there are some who
ser felices totalmente y hay algunos que
try to
intentan
live in their children the life that
vivir en sus hijos la vida que han
they have been able to live and that their children be
podido vivir ellos y que sus hijos sea
what their children do not want to be but what
lo que sus hijos no quieren ser sino lo
they want to be there are
que ellos quieren ser
other parents however they
hay otros padres que sin embargo lo
do it with good intentions so that they
hacen con buena intención para que lo
do it as if to say hey look for example
hace como diciendo oye mira por ejemplo
what I will do no listen do not be an
lo que yo haré no oye no hagáis el
idiot like I have done okay on the air
como he hecho yo vale al aire
if he reads [ __ ] as a pimp and I will transmit to him
si lee como chulo y le transmitiré
and I will let him see why they
y le dejaré ver por qué
should take advantage of their youth to
deberían aprovechar la juventud para
study and be useful people
estudiar y ser unas personas de provecho
Mexican the symbol kids I do not know until
mexicana la symbol chavales no sé hasta
how long I will last
qué hora voy a durar
the thing Dallas has this way of
la cosa dallas tiene esta forma de
thinking and thing he has had a vasectomy we
pensar y cosa se ha hecho la vasectomía
already know
ya lo sabemos
but from here to do it to eat  he
pero de aquí a que lo haga por comer le
blows his mind to his younger followers
el coco a sus seguidores menores
as they want us to see on the contrary it
como quieren hacernos ver del contrario
is not like that
no es así
Dallas is addressing his audience
dallas se está dirigiendo a su audiencia
that he assumes is the same age as
que él supone que de la misma edad que
him so he is telling his
él vale entonces está contando su
experience his thoughts
experiencia su pensamiento
as we do any youtube on
como hacemos cualquier youtube en
our page because I play our
nuestra página porque juego nuestro
daily
diario
dallas when he makes these statements he
dallas cuando hace estas afirmaciones no
is not referring to it is not him he is not
se está refiriendo no es él no está
thinking that he is addressing children
pensando que se está dirigiendo a niños
okay these people are presenting him
vale ya esta gente lo están poniendo
as if he were
como si fuera
some kind of pastor some kind of
una especie de pastor una especie de
pastor who has a sect of children here that he
pastor que tiene aquí una secta de niños
is brainwashing
a los que les está comiendo la cabeza
so that they think like him and that they are his
para que piensen como él y que sean su
cattle no matter what he is putting his way
ganado no dale él está poniendo su forma
of thinking as you see it and he is
de pensar como la vez y se está
addressing people that he understands are
dirigiendo a gente que él entiende que
his age okay
es de su edad vale
that seems extremely important to me to
eso me parece sumamente importante para
destroy whoever acne send it to me
destruir a quien el acné mandámelo por
through and tell me what it is retweet it is
pasar y dime qué es lo que retweet
very important to begin with the
es muy importante para empezar con el
context of this analysis not both
contexto de este análisis no ambas
good are the most abusive children are
buenos son los hijos más abusivos son
the parents it is that this depends on the case
los padres es que esto depende del caso
but I do not think it is the vast majority not even
pero no creo que sea la gran mayoría ni
remotely he
de coña
directly addresses the viewer who
interpela directamente al espectador que
is good
es bueno
and he does know  see and value not like
y él sí que sabe ver y valorar no como
their parents who will take advantage in fact
sus padres que se aprovecharán de hecho
Alvarez was turning into a
álvarez estaba convirtiendo en un
chihuahua for your parents who had them
chihuahua para tus padres que las tenía
six years ago
de la hace seis años
because it is not the same I put myself in my
porque no es lo mismo yo me pongo mi
place okay I put myself in my place it
lugar vale me pongo yo en mi lugar
is not the same my way of thinking when I
no es lo mismo mi forma de pensar cuando
was 18 19 years old than my way of thinking
tenía 18 19 años que mi forma de pensar
now with 35 okay in brawn I what I
de ahora con 35 vale en brawn yo cual
had when I was a teenager and my
tenía yo cuando era adolescente y mi
mother told me that she wanted me to study
madre me decía que quería que estudiara
that she wanted me to go to university that she
que quería que fuera la universidad que
was ashamed that I started working and
le daba pena que me pusiera a trabajar y
leave the studies with what with the
dejar a los estudios con lo que con la
mind that I had with the
mente que yo tenía con los estudiosos de
aviation scholars I believed that my mother
aviación yo me creía que mi madre me lo
told me because my mother wanted me to
decía porque mi madre quería que yo
be a
fuera
good student because of what they will say no so
buen estudiante por el qué dirán no para
that the neighbors and the family do not say
que las vecinas y la familia no diga
anything and look he is a brat who works there
nada y mira es un niñato que trabaja ahí
because my mother wanted to be able to boast of
porque mi madre quería poder presumir de
vintage and now I really realize
vintage y ahora realmente me doy cuenta
that it is not like that I now really
que no es así yo ahora realmente me di
realized that when your father is telling you
cuenta que cuando tu padre te están
something I
diciendo algo
feel so much for your well-being what happens that
tanto siento por tu bien lo que pasa que
when let's see he sends me
cuando a ver me manda
[Music]
[Música]
of guidelines and the key of  the whole
de directrices y la clave de todo el
thread is that the term does not exist there are no
hilo es que el término no existe no hay
studies that support the existence of
estudios que avalen la existencia del
grooming for social it takes them from the video
grooming para social los saca del vídeo
of dry tip of the thread if it is true
de seca punta del hilo si ya es verdad
if it is totally true it is based on
si totalmente es cierto está basado en
a thread from an aunt who was
un hilo de una tía que quienes les
doing it but well let's go in such a
hacían pero bueno vamos a ir de tal
way by analyzing her analysis
manera por analizando el análisis de
the thing is that today at 35 years old and that I
la cosa es que hoy con 35 años y que
have two children I know what a child wants I
tengo dos niños se lo que se quiere un
know that a child there will be no pets
sé que un hijo no habrá mascotas el
tourism is not like a puppy oh look I
turismo no es como un cachorrito ay mira
have a son I'm going to put a bow on him I'm going to
tengo un hijo voy a poner un lacito voy
put these clothes on him no I now know that
a ponerle esta ropa no yo ahora sé que
for me a nest
para mí un nido
would tear out an arm for me I would die for
arrancaría un brazo por mí moriría por
either of the two
cualquiera de los dos
literally that
literalmente
is not an exaggeration for you to say I would
esa no es una exageración que tú digas
not die but no no no literally I would
no moriría pero no no no literalmente
give whatever was in my life
moriría daría lo que fuera de mi vida
for either of the two whatever it is you
por cualquiera de los dos lo que fuera
always have to cut off the head so
siempre tienes que cortar la cabeza para
that one of them is well literally
que uno de ellos esté bien literal
understand and now I understand that in
entiende y ahora entiendo que en
any father when he is
cualquier padre cuando te está
advising you that translated for your own good
aconsejando eso traducido por tu bien
because tomorrow like me you will
porque el día de mañana como yo me
help me or YouTube I don't know how long it will
ayudarás o youtube no sé el tiempo que
last but I would be in the factory
me durará pero estaría en la fábrica
lifting for the  four in the morning
levantando para las cuatro a la mañana
putting up with so many things that if I
aguantando muchísimas cosas que si
had studied a degree then no and there has
hubiera estudiado una carrera pues no y
been more worth it I do
más ha habido valió
n't know if you understand
no sé si me entendéis
what the problem is the problem is
cuál es el problema el problema está en
that parents and children
que los padres y los hijos normalmente
are normally from very different generations from
son de generaciones muy diferentes de
very different times I mean I get along
tiempo muy diferente o sea yo me llevo
very well with my parents today and
muy bien con mis padres hoy por hoy y
I always get along very well with my parents
yo me llevo muy bien con mis padres
but we have a very different way of
pero tenemos una manera muy diferente de
thinking and many very different points of
pensar y muchos puntos muy diferentes de
things my mother is called upset
las cosas mi madre se llaman disgusto
because I got a tattoo well the hand you left
porque yo me tatué bueno la mano te ibas
and my mother doesn't sleep when she knows that the
y mi madre no duerme cuando sabe que al
next day I have a tattoo appointment
día siguiente tengo cita de tatuaje
and she doesn't sleep especially the suffocation because she thinks it's
y no duerme esp al sofoco porque lo ve
very bad because she doesn't like that I got a tattoo it
muy mal porque no le gusta que me tatué
may seem very nice to her while she
le puede parecer muy bonito en tanto
waits she doesn't like it anymore and she doesn't want her
espera ya no le gusta y no quiere que su
son to have tattoos it hurts him and I don't
hijo sea tattoos le duele y que no
understand why for my wonderful
entiendo por qué para mis maravillosos
Valencia political issues social issues
valència temas políticos temas sociales
chat shops parents and children are
chats shops los padres y los hijos
normally very different generations
normalmente somos generaciones muy
okay so the problem is in fact
vale entonces el problema es de hecho el
understanding many times very difficult
entendimiento muchas veces muy difícil
okay no matter how good intentions
vale por muy buena intención que tenga
a father and a mother have making your
un padre y una madre el hacerle ver a tu
child see that they are telling them the  things for
hijo que le está diciendo las cosas por
your own good and making your son understand that you
tu bien y hacerle entender a tu hijo que
want the best for him okay I don't know that's
quiere lo mejor para ello vale no sé es
the issue then what I see here is a
el tema entonces yo aquí lo que veas un
kid who doesn't understand his
chaval que no está entendiendo a sus
parents maybe
padres
their relationship for whatever reason has
a lo mejor su relación por lo que sea
n't been normal
por no ha sido la normal y corriente
okay I think I think
vale
that the majority of
yo creo yo creo que la mayoría de
families are like mine okay like
familias son como la mía vale en plan
well they had parents who have
bien que han tenido unos padres que han
given everything for their children and my father has
dado todo por sus hijos ya mi padre lo
given everything for me he knows
han dado todo por mí sabe
everything anything come on anything they've had a
todo cualquier cosa 'vamos cualquier
terrible time with me
cosa lo han pasado fatal conmigo
and what the majority of such this job
y lo que la mayoría de tal este trabajo
has had another different life and has seen
ha tenido otra vida diferente y ha visto
things from another perspective but from
las cosas de otra perspectiva pero de
there from there to the fact that he is a guy who is
ahí de ahí a que sea un tío que esté
scheming because here they are
maquinando porque aquí lo están
selling him as a guy who is
vendiendo como un tío que está
scheming I'm
maquinando
going to brainwash my sect of
voy a comer la cabeza a mi secta de
minors
menores
to be able to manipulate them as if I had
para poder manejarlos como si yo tuviera
a play controller
un mando de la play
this kid has explained those things to us
este chaval nos ha explicado esas cosas
in that video it's not crossing his
de ese vídeo no se le está pasando por
mind what I see here is a kid
la cabeza yo aquí lo que veo a un chaval
who is telling that and it's his mind he is
que está contando eso y es su mente está
talking to kids the same age
hablando con chavales de la misma edad
as him
que él
this is the way he presents
esta es la forma en la que presenta en
his book on wapa  dallas philosophy
wapa su libro filosofía de dallas de
whose existence is super thanks to which you get out do
cuya existencia super gracias a que sal
not expect me to take much care of the forms
no esperéis que cuide mucho las formas
or reviewed ceiling reading this work will be
ni revisados techo leer esta obra será
like simply chatting with a
como simplemente estar chateando con un
friend bond of trust see
amigo vínculo de confianza a ver
any other spill any I
cualquier otro vertido cualquier yo
was nor can I give an example or rather
estuve ni puedo poner de ejemplo o sea
this bond of trust
es que esto de vínculo de confianza
try to empathize and create such this
intentar empatizar y crear un tal esto
could give an example to several
podría poner de ejemplo a varios
youtubers of those who have shared this
youtubers de los que han compartido este
thread
hilo
mentor and example to follow
mentor y ejemplo a seguir
I believe that any youtube or the vast
yo creo que cualquier youtube o la gran
majority depends on the content but we have
mayoría depende del contenido pero hemos
made blogs
hecho blogs
trying that our followers are
intentando que nuestros seguidores sean
of any age learn from our
de la edad que sea aprendan de nuestros
mistakes of our experiences
errores de nuestras vivencias
with which with the simple fact that
con lo cual con el simple hecho de que
this serves some of you to
esto sirva a algunos de vosotros para
progress in your lives and mature
progresar en vuestra vida y madurar
mentally and socially before time
mental y socialmente antes de tiempo te
value you consider yourself an adult even if you are not
valore considera adulto aunque no lo
but who is assuming that
seas pero quién está dando por hecho que
dallas
dallas
considers that its followers are not
considera que sus seguidores no son
adults
adultos
so the things that I will tell you and I will
por lo que las cosas que os contaré e
analyze may sometimes
iré analizando puede que en ocasiones os
sound a little abrupt or perhaps lacking
suenen un poco brusca o tal vez carente
in morals but they are things that nobody is going to
de moral pero son cosas que nadie va a
say or teach not even your
decir ni enseñar ni siquiera a vuestros
own parents  intimacy and
propios padres intimidad y
representation of parents or figures I
representación de los padres o figuras
could put I'm not going to give names but I
podría poner no voy a dar nombres pero
could put more than one youtube see
podría poner a más de un youtube ver de
what they have shared the thread or people who
lo que han compartido el hilo o gente de
defend these people
las que defienden esta gente
that their channels have told things to
que sus canales le han contado cosas a
their followers and have spoken about topics
sus seguidores y le han hablado de temas
that parents would not do
que los padres no lo harían
bitter thousands for example you are going to
amarga miles por ejemplo tú me vas a
tell me amarna thousands that you on your channel
decir amarna miles que tú en tu canal no
have not spoken with your followers things
ha hablado con tus seguidores cosas
that your father would not tell you
que su padre no le contaría
what the balls no
qué huevos no
in the video making a fool of the
en el vídeo dejando en ridículo a la
witches' house against me admits to having
casa de brujas contra mí admite haber
had a conversation with a
tenido una conversación con una fan de
16 year old fan and asking her are you a virgin when you
16 años y preguntarle eres virgen cuando
start [ __ ] you will feel much
empieces a te sentirás mucho
better about yourself he denies that it is
mejor contigo misma niega que sea
problematic since his intention is to
problemático ya que su intención es de
flirt or rather the video
ligar o sea el vídeo
the video itself was already four
el vídeo ya de por sí era de hace cuatro
years old and the supposed conversation with a
años y la supuesta conversación con una
16 year old fan when it was
fan de 16 años cuando fue
in short he has built a bond of
en resumen ha construido un vínculo de
trust with his audience they see him as
confianza con su audiencia lo ven como
a friend of those who are mixing
un amigo de las que están mezclando
things up to give context to all this
cosas para darle un contexto a todo esto
that they do not have to know why this
que no tienen saber por qué esta
conversation we would have to see when it was that he
conversación habría que ver cuándo fue
answered what it is that I ask him I do
que contestó qué es lo que le pregunto
not know
no sé
here brings me the sister no  that according to
aquí me trae la hermana no que según
this person would have made videos of his
esta persona habría hecho vídeos de su
sister with a context of monitoring
hermana con un contexto de seguimiento
her affective sexual development
de su desarrollo afectivo sexual
in a humorous way, he plays the role of the
en clave de humor juega el papel del mar
older sea that must protect the purity of my
mayor que debe proteger la pureza de mi
sister, he
hermana
also tells her that the
también le dice que el baño de
disabled bathroom is the best place to
minusválido es el mejor sitio para
do it in front of innocent comments,
hacerlo ante comentarios inocentes
several times he makes jokes with a double
varias veces hace bromas con un doble
sexual meaning, for example the boy
sentido sexual por ejemplo el niño
says that she usually complains when he
cuenta que ella se suele quejar cuando
pulled her hair it gets caught
le tiró del pelo se le engancha
and Dallas I hope it is not that it is not
y dallas espero que no sea que no sea
true context of a sexual party
cierto contexto de fiesta sexual
well here what I can tell you
bueno aquí lo que os puedo decir
what I can say is that Dallas's sister is
lo que puedo decir que la hermana de
14 years old
dallas tiene 14 años
yes 14 years old and that she is not 10 years old as
si 14 años y que no tiene 10 años como
the titles of the videos say
dicen los títulos de los vídeos
normalizing in soft taxis and this type
normalizando en taxis suaves y este tipo
of topic and conversation between a child and
de tema y conversación entre un niño y
an adult a girl was not 16 is 16 I do
un adulto una niña no tenía 16 tiene 16
n't think she will be 14 15
no creo que tendrá 14 15
already about the 10 year old videos I m
ya lo de los vídeos de 10 años me m
in another one that he makes with the line the
en otro que hace con la línea el punto
climax of the video and the clip bay is to
álgido del vídeo y el clip bay es
discover that when writing
descubrir que al escribir el nombre de
her name followed by the letter p among the
ella seguido de la letra p entre las
most popular searches on google
búsquedas más populares de google
pac appears  and feet
aparece pac y pies
she doesn't know what country the
ella no sabe lo que país se le explica
content of them is explained to her it is her face
contenido de ellas es una su cara
singing the ration
cantando la ración
at the moment in which it was seen it was made
en el momento en el que se vio se hizo
so that it only came out when they put the p
para que sólo salía cuando ponían la p
but now in the second search that
pero ahora en la segunda búsqueda que
google suggests
sugiere google
here what is being criticized is the
aquí lo que se está criticando es los
sick people who search for this to the sick people
enfermos que buscan esto a los enfermos
who search for this is google I will
que buscan esto es google
continue in a moment the important thing remains
sigo en un rato queda lo importante
here he has posted a video that has been thrown to him
aquí ha puesto un vídeo que se le ha
true yes it is true
verdad sí es verdad
sexualized content has several
contenido sexualizado tiene varios
cartoon porn videos
vídeos de porno de dibujos
it is some genitals of the clips but it
es unas genitales de los clips pero
explicitly narrates what is happening he
narra explícitamente lo que está pasando
says that he would love for mabel
dice que le encantaría que mabel
characters of 10 years to be his boyfriend
personajes de 10 años fuera su novio
good example about this mabel they have
ejemplo bueno sobre esto de mabel me han
sent me something
mandado una cosa
that she does not show in the video
que ella no saca en el vídeo
obviously but they have sent me
evidentemente pero me han mandado una
something that I am going to show you
cosa que os voy a enseñar yo
and that apparently this subject of mabel
y que al parecer el tema este de mabel
is some drawings well it is a joke that
es unos dibujitos pues es una broma que
he had with his ex girlfriend and here is his
él tenía con su ex novia y aquí está su
ex girlfriend who has a you and you can
ex novia que tiene un tú y lo podéis
search for it to see if it focuses and says it is very
buscar a ver si enfoca y dice es muy
pretty but it is babel and I are the same
bonito pero es babel y yo somos la misma
person
persona
or so apparently it is  a joke
o sea que por lo visto es una broma que
he had with his ex girlfriend
él tenía con su ex novia
in which he called his ex girlfriend Mabel
en el que a su exnovia la llamaba mabel
okay
vale
this was passed to me this afternoon and well it
esto me lo han pasado esta tarde y bueno
seems to give a little bit of
parece ser que le da un poquito de
context to this topic it doesn't
contexto a este tema no
say that since he can't leave the links he
dice que como no puede dejar los enlaces
says the titles out loud so you
dice los títulos en voz alta para que lo
can search for it he
puedas buscar
has several lives talking about sex
tiene varios vida hablando sobre el sexo
like Jordi While and a bunch of
como jordi while y un montón de
youtubers
youtubers
we have an adult broadcasting to his
tenemos a un adulto transmitiendo a su
audience of minors minors in
audiencia de menores menores en
capital letters okay
mayúscula vale
sex is a necessity well it would be
que el sexo a una necesidad bueno fuera
because it's not an audience of minors let's
porque no es una audiencia de menores
see the
a ver
logical thing is to put a girl
que lo lógico es ponerse una chica con
they've flirted with and they've hooked up with you
la que han ligado y te han enrollado
ironically he says real men
irónicamente dice los hombres de verdad
don't do that we
no hacemos eso
give you a foot massage and then
te hacemos un masaje en los pies y luego
you can go home in peace and we're not
te puede ir a tu casa tranquila y no te
going to penetrate you even if we're
vamos a penetrar aunque estemos hecho de
hard on
erección
in fact here to make it crystal clear let's
de hecho aquí para que quede clarísimo a
see this this thread the Chileans because it
ver este este hilo los chilenos porque
's the one that ingrid has retweeted vales
es el que ha retwitteado ingrid vales
message that transmits if they have flirted with
mensaje que transmite si han ligado con
a boy and have gotten together with
un chico y ha llegado a enrollarse con
him you
él
can't say no and go
no puede decirle que no e irte tranquila
home in peace if you didn't want to not have
a tu casa si no querías no haberlo
provoked him  now what touches reality the
provocado ahora lo que toca realidad el
irreversible consent you can say
consentimiento irreversible puedes decir
no as soon as you stop feeling comfortable
que no en cuanto deje de sentirte cómoda
regardless of whether you have flirted
independientemente de si han ligado
before your partner decides or not and even
antes decides tu pareja o no e incluso
during a sexual relationship and the other
durante una relación sexual y la otra
person must respect it throughout the
persona debe respetarlo durante el
duration of the sexual relationship both
tiempo que dura la relación sexual ambos
must be interested in making sure that both
deben interesarse asegurarse que las dos
people want to enjoy okay it is
personas quieren disfrutar vale se
supposed to be in reality well that it
supone que está en la realidad bueno que
is in fact what is supposed to be
la es de hecho lo que se supone que esté
the message that according to her she
el mensaje que según ella está les
wants to convey to them now what would you go to
quiere transmitir ahora lo que irían a
retweet if this
retuitear si esto
as a forensic psychologist with experience
como psicóloga forense con experiencia
in gender violence expertise
en peritaje de violencia de género
I am going to compare this evidence that they
voy a comparar estas pruebas que
present to show that she has not
presentan ala para demostrar que no ha
abused
maltratado
well there are 11 pages that I did not know how to
bueno son 11 páginas que no lo sabía
read in full okay there was no abuse because
leer entera vale no hubo maltrato porque
the girls did not study how
las chicas no estudiaron cómo actuaría
a victim would act a real victim does not want to
una víctima una víctima real no quiere
talk about her experience later how have they
hablar de su experiencia después como
done to her if she does not comply with the
han hecho de ella si no cumple el
precise service of the victims they have not
preciso servicio de las víctimas no han
suffered abuse there is no
sufrido maltrato no existe un perfil de
victim profile in the universal form of victim
víctima en la forma universal de víctima
someone who can get a
a alguien que puede conseguir a una
girl without harassing her has no reason to
chica sin acosarla no tiene motivos para
reach her pedophiles rapists and
alcanzarla los pedófilos violadores y
harassers are not young people with
acosadores no son personas jóvenes con
money yes famous
dinero si famosos
the  harassment abuse or rape
el acoso maltrato o violación a menudo
are often manifestations of power over the
son manifestaciones de poder sobre la
victim they are not resources for those who
víctima no son recursos para quien no
cannot get the girl I'm
puede conseguir la chica
not going to read the 11 points because
no voy a leer los 11 puntos porque se
the live show is getting too long you
nos está yendo el directo larguísimo lo
have it here if you want to read it but my
tenéis aquí si queréis leerlo pero es mi
conclusion is that
conclusión es que
by putting the possibility of a
al estar poniendo aquí la posibilidad de
myth here that when I made the myth she was
mito que cuando hice el mito se está
referring to Dallas' arguments and
refiriendo a los argumentos de dallas y
then she imposes a reality here in a
luego ella impone una realidad aquí de
way well I was going to say indirectly but it does
manera bueno iba a decir indirecta pero
n't seem so indirect to me she
no me parece tan indirecta
would be making an accusation
estaría haciendo una acusación
because you're saying that
porque estás diciendo que
Dallas' arguments are not
estos argumentos de dallas no son
valid that the reality would be this
válidos que la realidad sería ésta
conclusion appears in its content all
conclusión aparece en su contenido todas
the strategies that characterize
las estrategias que caracteriza al
traditional grooming these strategies
grooming tradicional estas estrategias
anyway swear words
en fin
for me he's accusing there's a
le tacos para mí él está acusando hay
lot that I've skipped the one who's
mucho que me he saltado el que estoy
here with a quick view
aquí con la vista rápidamente
this is happening right in front of our
esto está pasando delante de nuestra
noses and we don't know how many millions
narices y no sabemos a cuántos millones
of minors it has 10,000 subscribers it
de menores tiene 10.000 suscriptores
could be affecting and it's very dangerous
puede estar afectando y es muy peligroso
for me if you're pointing it out
para mí si lo estás señalando
or rather not saying the literal words
o sea no dice las palabras literales en
seriously everything a
serio todo lo
dick
una
he gave himself everything a
él se dio todo
crazy everything you've given  36 thousand
loco todo lo que has dado 36 mil
what the [ __ ]
qué
in front of 80,000 he has
ante 80.000
given everything today like 120 thousand there is in
todo lo ha dado hoy como 120 mil hay en
total I'm going to give you referee at least
total te voy a dar árbitro como menos
at least no thank you thank you
como mínimo no
very much really
gracias muchísimas gracias de verdad
for me if he is accusing him or rather it's
para mí si le está acusando o sea es
like saying you know
como decir sabes
this seems to me a little even
esto me parece un poco incluso el modus
Joana's modus operandi is not good I
operandi de joana no es bueno yo lo
'm letting it fall interpret it however
estoy dejando caer interpretarlo como
you want and it's your fault if you interpret it
quieras y es tu culpa si lo interpretas
like that
así
basically if you are saying that there are
básicamente si tú estás diciendo que hay
acts of grooming in his videos you are assuming you are
acciones de grooming en sus vídeos
assuming that his audience is smaller that he
hecho que su audiencia es menor que él
is aware that they are smaller
es consciente de que de que son menores
things that you get them from his father
cosas que te los sacas del papá
but you get them from his father being with him you are
pero sacas del papo estando con él estás
assuming that not only do I take
dando por hecho que no solamente trato
for granted that this audience is smaller
por hecho que esa audiencia es menor
but that he is aware and acts
sino que él es consciente y actúa a
knowing that his audience is smaller
sabiendas de que su audiencia es menor
that he is manipulating them to create a
que la está manipulando para crear un
bond with them okay
vínculo con ellos vale
and that in addition
y que además
he is making excuses to say
él está poniendo unas excusas para decir
that he has not abused when
que él no ha maltratado cuando sin
however the reality is different
embargo la realidad es otra
or rather what does it mean when you
o sea que quiere es decir cuando le
are telling someone that their
estás diciendo a alguien que sus
arguments to say that they have not
argumentos para decir que no ha
abused  you are not worth it because the reality
maltratado no vales porque la realidad
is different
es otra
when I touch on said that there is no
cuando tocaré a dicho que no existe
slander, I am not so clear, I
calumnia yo no lo tengo tan claro yo no
am not a jurist, I can be wrong, I am not a
soy jurista me puedo equivocar ni soy
jurist, I am not a lawyer,
jurista ni soy abogado ni soy
nor am I a specialist in laws, okay, I consider that I understand a lot of laws because of the things that I have had to live through, the things that I am living through and all the cases that have been analyzed, okay, I am not a jurist, I can be wrong, I am not an
jurista me puedo equivocar ni soy ningún
expert, I am not a lawyer, nor do I have any
experto ni soy abogado ni tengo nada de
legal studies,
estudio de derecho
but slander for me is accusing
pero una calumnia para mí es acusar a
someone of a crime if you already have
alguien de un delito si tú tienes ya a
websites to accuse Aryans where he and he
una webs a acusar arios donde él y está
knows that he is not guilty, okay, if you
sabiendas que no es culpable vale si tú
have some judges who
le tienes unos jueces que a este chaval
have declared this kid innocent, they have
lo han declarado inocente lo han
acquitted him of each and every one of the
absuelto de todas y cada una de las
charges that have been filed against him, which have not
denuncias que le han puesto que no han
been few,
sido pocas
and that kid transmits it in his videos, I have
y ese chaval lo transmite en sus vídeos
been acquitted for this, for this, for
he sido absuelto por esto por esto por
this, the judges and the judges
esto por esto los jueces y los jueces
have declared and have considered
han manifestado y han considerado
that I am not an abuser because they have
que no soy un maltratador porque han
seen this, you have seen the others, they have seen this,
visto esto has visto a los otros han
who are you, a psychologist and a doctor,
quién eres tú una psicóloga y doctor
come on
anda
to state that no no that there were three
para manifestar que no no que eran tres
female judges is that there are many other
magistradas es que son muchos otros
cases the case of Ingrid the trials com
casos el caso de ingrid los juicios com
viales not only the three female judges is
viales no sólo las tres magistradas es
that there are more things
que hay más cosas
who are you to say that the
quién eres tú para decir que los
arguments that he has expressed that he
argumentos que él ha expresado que él
will have expressed the arguments of the
habrá expresado los argumentos de la
brand to the judges who you to
brand a los jueces quienes tú para
come and say that is not valid what you
llegar y decir eso no vale lo que tú
are saying to say that you are an
estás diciendo para decir que eres un
abuser is not valid or rather really here you do
maltratador no vale o sea realmente aquí
not see accusations of crime he is
no veis acusaciones de delito está
saying that in his videos
diciendo que en sus vídeos
if there are or if there are accusations of crime
si hay o si va a acusaciones de delito
here I did
aquí
not know how to tell you because I am not good
no sabía deciros porque no soy bueno
regarding if this could be prosecuted
respecto si esto se podría perseguir por
criminally as a right to honor for
lo penal en plan derecho al honor por
slander or if it could be prosecuted
calumnias o si se podría perseguir más
rather for I think rather
bien por yo creo que más bien por lo
civilly for right to honor I would have more
civil por derecho al honor tendría más
security but I am not an expert in audio
seguridad pero de audio no soy ningún
but since you are telling me
experto pero ya que me estáis diciendo
that he is not accusing him he is already saying you are
que no lo está acusando ya está diciendo
affirming at the moment he is
estás afirmando de momento está
affirming that in his videos there are group actions
afirmando que en sus vídeos hay acciones
and he is affirming that this action is
y está afirmando que esa acción es de
grooming he is doing them
grooming las está haciendo
assuming the youtuber that his
dando el youtuber por hecho que su
audience is minors taking only from the
audiencia son menores sacando sólo del
father
papá
and then the key  and then he adds that his
y luego la llave y luego añade que su
argument to say that he is not an
argumento para decir que no es
abuser is not valid
maltratador no vale
if you do not see the accusations here,
si ustedes no vea aquí las acusaciones
I do see them, I could be wrong, I see them,
yo sí la veo me puedo equivocar yo las
okay, but do not worry,
veo
David Bravo has gone and David Bravo is going to
ido david bravo y david bravo le va a
tell him that nothing is wrong with that thread
decir que no pasa nada con ese hilo
but if I see it, as soon as I
pero yo si lo veo
make a video about this, well,
nada más hacer un vídeo sobre esto
we will react to the video of the fairy, I
pues reaccionaremos al vídeo del hada
was going to read your thread but since the
iba a leer tu hilo pero esto ya que el
video I am very sorry since the video I am
vídeo siento mucho ya que el vídeo me
going to study, guys, what book do they
voy a chavales estudia qué libro
leave me walls to the pse or on it gives the
me dejan paredes al pse o sobre el da la
slope but I am going to react to them
pendiente pero los voy a reaccionar
tomorrow, okay,
mañana vale
the chest, I am going to save, I am going to save
el cofre voy a ahorrar voy a ahorrar
a lot more, okay
mucho más vale
[Music]
[Música]
Thank you very much to everyone for
muchísimas gracias a todos por el día de
today, it is incredible, thank you very much for
hoy es increíble muchísimas gracias por
the support, week that a couple of
el apoyo semana que a un par de cosas
pending things, a couple of jumps that I have to
pendientes de un par de saltos que tengo
tell about Dallas
que contar sobre dallas
but but I can't take it anymore,
pero pero no puedo más
the view of habitat to the computer to live,
la vista de hábitat al ordenador
to live like turbo plan
a vivir a vivir como turbo plan